<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 Chronicles on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/2-chronicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 Chronicles on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/2-chronicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Chronicles - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/14-2-chronicles-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/14-2-chronicles-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>2 Chronicles - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV) [1:1] And Solomon the son of David was strengthened in his kingdom, and Jehovah his God was with him, and magnified him exceedingly.
[1:2] And Solomon spake unto all Israel, to the captains of thousands and of hundreds, and to the judges, and to every prince in all Israel, the heads of the fathers&amp;rsquo; `houses&amp;rsquo;.
[1:3] So Solomon, and all the assembly with him, went to the high place that was at Gibeon; for there was the tent of meeting of God, which Moses the servant of Jehovah had made in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Chronicles - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/14-2-chronicles-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/14-2-chronicles-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>2 Chronicles - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] And Solomon, the son of David, made himself strong in his kingdom, and the Lord his God was with him, and made him very great.
[1:2] And Solomon sent word to all Israel, to the captains of thousands and of hundreds and to the judges and to every chief in all Israel, heads of their families.
[1:3] Then Solomon, and all the men of Israel with him, went to the high place at Gibeon, because the Tent of meeting of God, which Moses, the servant of the Lord, had made in the waste land, was there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Chronicles - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/14-2-chronicles-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/14-2-chronicles-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>2 Chronicles - King James Version (KJV) [1:1] And Solomon the son of David was strengthened in his kingdom, and the LORD his God was with him, and magnified him exceedingly.
[1:2] Then Solomon spake unto all Israel, to the captains of thousands and of hundreds, and to the judges, and to every governor in all Israel, the chief of the fathers.
[1:3] So Solomon, and all the congregation with him, went to the high place that was at Gibeon; for there was the tabernacle of the congregation of God, which Moses the servant of the LORD had made in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Chronicles - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/14-2-chronicles-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/14-2-chronicles-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>2 Chronicles - World English Bible (WEB) [1:1] Solomon the son of David was strengthened in his kingdom, and Yahweh his God was with him, and magnified him exceedingly.
[1:2] Solomon spoke to all Israel, to the captains of thousands and of hundreds, and to the judges, and to every prince in all Israel, the heads of the fathers&amp;rsquo; [houses].
[1:3] So Solomon, and all the assembly with him, went to the high place that was at Gibeon; for there was the tent of meeting of God, which Moses the servant of Yahweh had made in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Chronicles - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/14-2-chronicles-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/14-2-chronicles-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>2 Chronicles - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And strengthen himself doth Solomon son of David over his kingdom, and Jehovah his God `is&amp;rsquo; with him, and maketh him exceedingly great.
[1:2] And Solomon saith to all Israel, to heads of the thousands, and of the hundreds, and to judges, and to every honourable one of all Israel, heads of the fathers,
[1:3] and they go &amp;ndash; Solomon, and all the assembly with him &amp;ndash; to the high place that `is&amp;rsquo; in Gibeon, for there hath been God&amp;rsquo;s tent of meeting, that Moses, servant of Jehovah, made in the wilderness,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>