<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>YLT on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/ylt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in YLT on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/ylt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Chronicles - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/13-1-chronicles-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/13-1-chronicles-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>1 Chronicles - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Adam, Sheth, Enosh,
[1:2] Kenan, Mahalaleel, Jered,
[1:3] Henoch, Methuselah, Lamech,
[1:4] Noah, Shem, Ham, and Japheth.
[1:5] Sons of Japheth: Gomer and Magog, and Madai, and Javan, and Tubal, and Meshech, and Tiras.
[1:6] And sons of Gomer: Ashchenaz, and Riphath, and Togarmah.
[1:7] And sons of Javan: Elisha, and Tarshishah, Kittim, and Dodanim.
[1:8] Sons of Ham: Cush, and Mizraim, Put, and Canaan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/46-1-corinthians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/46-1-corinthians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>1 Corinthians - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, a called apostle of Jesus Christ, through the will of God, and Sosthenes the brother,
[1:2] to the assembly of God that is in Corinth, to those sanctified in Christ Jesus, called saints, with all those calling upon the name of our Lord Jesus Christ in every place &amp;ndash; both theirs and ours:
[1:3] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 John - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/62-1-john-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/62-1-john-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>1 John - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] That which was from the beginning, that which we have heard, that which we have seen with our eyes, that which we did behold, and our hands did handle, concerning the Word of the Life &amp;ndash;
[1:2] and the Life was manifested, and we have seen, and do testify, and declare to you the Life, the age-during, which was with the Father, and was manifested to us &amp;ndash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Kings - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/11-1-kings-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/11-1-kings-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>1 Kings - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And king David `is&amp;rsquo; old, entering into days, and they cover him with garments, and he hath no heat,
[1:2] and his servants say to him, `Let them seek for my lord the king a young woman, a virgin, and she hath stood before the king, and is to him a companion, and hath lain in thy bosom, and my lord the king hath heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Peter - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/60-1-peter-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/60-1-peter-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>1 Peter - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Peter, an apostle of Jesus Christ, to the choice sojourners of the dispersion of Pontus, Galatia, Cappadocia, Asia, and Bithynia,
[1:2] according to a foreknowledge of God the Father, in sanctification of the Spirit, to obedience and sprinkling of the blood of Jesus Christ: Grace to you and peace be multiplied!
[1:3] Blessed `is&amp;rsquo; the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who, according to the abundance of His kindness did beget us again to a living hope, through the rising again of Jesus Christ out of the dead,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Samuel - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/9-1-samuel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/9-1-samuel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>1 Samuel - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And there is a certain man of Ramathaim-Zophim, of the hill-country of Ephraim, and his name `is&amp;rsquo; Elkanah, son of Jeroham, son of Elihu, son of Tohu, son of Zuph, and Ephrathite,
[1:2] and he hath two wives, the name of the one `is&amp;rsquo; Hannah, and the name of the second Peninnah, and Peninnah hath children, and Hannah hath no children.
[1:3] And that man hath gone up out of his city from time to time, to bow himself, and to sacrifice, before Jehovah of Hosts, in Shiloh, and there `are&amp;rsquo; two sons of Eli, Hophni and Phinehas, priests to Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Thessalonians - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/52-1-thessalonians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/52-1-thessalonians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>1 Thessalonians - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, and Silvanus, and Timotheus, to the assembly of Thessalonians in God the Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ: Grace to you, and peace, from God our Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ!
[1:2] We give thanks to God always for you all, making mention of you in our prayers,
[1:3] unceasingly remembering of you the work of the faith, and the labour of the love, and the endurance of the hope, of our Lord Jesus Christ, in the presence of our God and Father,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Timothy - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/54-1-timothy-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/54-1-timothy-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>1 Timothy - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ, according to a command of God our Saviour, and of the Lord Jesus Christ our hope,
[1:2] to Timotheus &amp;ndash; genuine child in faith: Grace, kindness, peace, from God our Father, and Christ Jesus our Lord,
[1:3] according as I did exhort thee to remain in Ephesus &amp;ndash; I going on to Macedonia &amp;ndash; that thou mightest charge certain not to teach any other thing,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Chronicles - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/14-2-chronicles-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/14-2-chronicles-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>2 Chronicles - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And strengthen himself doth Solomon son of David over his kingdom, and Jehovah his God `is&amp;rsquo; with him, and maketh him exceedingly great.
[1:2] And Solomon saith to all Israel, to heads of the thousands, and of the hundreds, and to judges, and to every honourable one of all Israel, heads of the fathers,
[1:3] and they go &amp;ndash; Solomon, and all the assembly with him &amp;ndash; to the high place that `is&amp;rsquo; in Gibeon, for there hath been God&amp;rsquo;s tent of meeting, that Moses, servant of Jehovah, made in the wilderness,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Corinthians - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/47-2-corinthians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/47-2-corinthians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>2 Corinthians - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ, through the will of God, and Timotheus the brother, to the assembly of God that is in Corinth, with all the saints who are in all Achaia:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God our Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ!
[1:3] Blessed `is&amp;rsquo; God, even the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, the Father of the mercies, and God of all comfort,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 John - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/63-2-john-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/63-2-john-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>2 John - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] The Elder to the choice Kyria, and to her children, whom I love in truth, and not I only, but also all those having known the truth,
[1:2] because of the truth that is remaining in us, and with us shall be to the age,
[1:3] there shall be with you grace, kindness, peace, from God the Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ, the Son of the Father, in truth and love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/12-2-kings-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/12-2-kings-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>2 Kings - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And Moab transgresseth against Israel after the death of Ahab,
[1:2] and Ahaziah falleth through the lattice in his upper chamber that is&#39; in Samaria, and is sick, and sendeth messengers, and saith unto them, Go ye, inquire of Baal-Zebub god of Ekron if I recover from this sickness.&amp;rsquo;
[1:3] And a messenger of Jehovah hath spoken unto Elijah the Tishbite, `Rise, go up to meet the messengers of the king of Samaria, and speak unto them, Is it because there is not a God in Israel &amp;ndash; ye are going to inquire of Baal Zebub god of Ekron?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Peter - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/61-2-peter-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/61-2-peter-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>2 Peter - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Simeon Peter, a servant and an apostle of Jesus Christ, to those who did obtain a like precious faith with us in the righteousness of our God and Saviour Jesus Christ:
[1:2] Grace to you, and peace be multiplied in the acknowledgement of God and of Jesus our Lord!
[1:3] As all things to us His divine power (the things pertaining unto life and piety) hath given, through the acknowledgement of him who did call us through glory and worthiness,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Samuel - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/10-2-samuel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/10-2-samuel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>2 Samuel - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And it cometh to pass, after the death of Saul, that David hath returned from smiting the Amalekite, and David dwelleth in Ziklag two days,
[1:2] and it cometh to pass, on the third day, that lo, a man hath come in out of the camp from Saul, and his garments `are&amp;rsquo; rent, and earth on his head; and it cometh to pass, in his coming in unto David, that he falleth to the earth, and doth obeisance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Thessalonians - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/53-2-thessalonians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/53-2-thessalonians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>2 Thessalonians - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, and Silvanus, and Timotheus, to the assembly of Thessalonians in God our Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ:
[1:2] Grace to you, and peace, from God our Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ!
[1:3] We ought to give thanks to God always for you, brethren, as it is meet, because increase greatly doth your faith, and abound doth the love of each one of you all, to one another;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Timothy - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/55-2-timothy-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/55-2-timothy-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>2 Timothy - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ, through the will of God, according to a promise of life that `is&amp;rsquo; in Christ Jesus,
[1:2] to Timotheus, beloved child: Grace, kindness, peace, from God the Father, and Christ Jesus our Lord!
[1:3] I am thankful to God, whom I serve from progenitors in a pure conscience, that unceasingly I have remembrance concerning thee in my supplications night and day,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 John - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/64-3-john-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/64-3-john-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>3 John - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] The Elder to Gaius the beloved, whom I love in truth!
[1:2] beloved, concerning all things I desire thee to prosper, and to be in health, even as thy soul doth prosper,
[1:3] for I rejoiced exceedingly, brethren coming and testifying of the truth in thee, even as thou in truth dost walk;
[1:4] greater than these things I have no joy, that I may hear of my children in truth walking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acts - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/44-acts-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/44-acts-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Acts - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] The former account, indeed, I made concerning all things, O Theophilus, that Jesus began both to do and to teach,
[1:2] till the day in which, having given command, through the Holy Spirit, to the apostles whom he did choose out, he was taken up,
[1:3] to whom also he did present himself alive after his suffering, in many certain proofs, through forty days being seen by them, and speaking the things concerning the reign of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amos - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/30-amos-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/30-amos-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Amos - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Words of Amos &amp;ndash; who hath been among herdsmen of Tekoa &amp;ndash; that he hath seen concerning Israel, in the days of Uzziah king of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam son of Joash king of Israel, two years before the shaking;
[1:2] and he saith: Jehovah from Zion doth roar, And from Jerusalem giveth forth His voice, And mourned have pastures of the shepherds, And withered hath the top of Carmel!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colossians - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/51-colossians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/51-colossians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Colossians - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ through the will of God, and Timotheus the brother,
[1:2] to the saints in Colossae, and to the faithful brethren in Christ: Grace to you, and peace from God our Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ!
[1:3] We give thanks to the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, always praying for you,
[1:4] having heard of your faith in Christ Jesus, and of the love that `is&amp;rsquo; to all the saints,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/27-daniel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/27-daniel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Daniel - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] In the third year of the reign of Jehoiakim king of Judah, come hath Nebuchadnezzar king of Babylon to Jerusalem, and layeth siege against it;
[1:2] and the Lord giveth into his hand Jehoiakim king of Judah, and some of the vessels of the house of God, and he bringeth them in to&#39; the land of Shinar, to&amp;rsquo; the house of his god, and the vessels he hath brought in `to&amp;rsquo; the treasure-house of his god.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/5-deuteronomy-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/5-deuteronomy-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Deuteronomy - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] These `are&amp;rsquo; the words which Moses hath spoken unto all Israel, beyond the Jordan, in the wilderness, in the plain over-against Suph, between Paran and Tophel, and Laban, and Hazeroth, and Di-Zahab;
[1:2] eleven days&amp;rsquo; from Horeb, the way of mount Seir, unto Kadesh-Barnea.
[1:3] And it cometh to pass in the fortieth year, in the eleventh month, on the first of the month hath Moses spoken unto the sons of Israel according to all that Jehovah hath commanded him concerning them;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecclesiastes - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/21-ecclesiastes-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/21-ecclesiastes-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Ecclesiastes - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Words of a preacher, son of David, king in Jerusalem:
[1:2] Vanity of vanities, said the Preacher, Vanity of vanities: the whole `is&amp;rsquo; vanity.
[1:3] What advantage `is&amp;rsquo; to man by all his labour that he laboureth at under the sun?
[1:4] A generation is going, and a generation is coming, and the earth to the age is standing.
[1:5] Also, the sun hath risen, and the sun hath gone in, and unto its place panting it is rising there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ephesians - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/49-ephesians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/49-ephesians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Ephesians - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ through the will of God, to the saints who are in Ephesus, and to the faithful in Christ Jesus:
[1:2] Grace to you, and peace from God our Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ!
[1:3] Blessed `is&amp;rsquo; the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who did bless us in every spiritual blessing in the heavenly places in Christ,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/17-esther-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/17-esther-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Esther - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And it cometh to pass, in the days of Ahasuerus &amp;ndash; he `is&amp;rsquo; Ahasuerus who is reigning from Hodu even unto Cush, seven and twenty and a hundred provinces &amp;ndash;
[1:2] in those days, at the sitting of the king Ahasuerus on the throne of his kingdom, that `is&amp;rsquo; in Shushan the palace,
[1:3] in the third year of his reign, he hath made a banquet to all his heads and his servants; of the force of Persia and Media, the chiefs and heads of the provinces `are&amp;rsquo; before him,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exodus - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/2-exodus-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/2-exodus-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Exodus - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And these `are&amp;rsquo; the names of the sons of Israel who are coming into Egypt with Jacob; a man and his household have they come;
[1:2] Reuben, Simeon, Levi, and Judah,
[1:3] Issachar, Zebulun, and Benjamin,
[1:4] Dan, and Naphtali, Gad, and Asher.
[1:5] And all the persons coming out of the thigh of Jacob are seventy persons; as to Joseph, he was in Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/26-ezekiel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/26-ezekiel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Ezekiel - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And it cometh to pass, in the thirtieth year, in the fourth month&#39;, in the fifth of the month, and I am&amp;rsquo; in the midst of the Removed by the river Chebar, the heavens have been opened, and I see visions of God.
[1:2] In the fifth of the month &amp;ndash; it is the fifth year of the removal of the king Jehoiachin &amp;ndash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezra - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/15-ezra-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/15-ezra-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Ezra - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And in the first year of Cyrus king of Persia, at the completion of the word of Jehovah from the mouth of Jeremiah, hath Jehovah waked up the spirit of Cyrus king of Persia, and he causeth an intimation to pass over into all his kingdom, and also in writing, saying,
[1:2] Thus said Cyrus king of Persia, All kingdoms of the earth hath Jehovah, God of the heavens, given to me, and He hath laid a charge on me to build to Him a house in Jerusalem, that is&amp;rsquo; in Judah;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galatians - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/48-galatians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/48-galatians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Galatians - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, an apostle &amp;ndash; not from men, nor through man, but through Jesus Christ, and God the Father, who did raise him out of the dead &amp;ndash;
[1:2] and all the brethren with me, to the assemblies of Galatia:
[1:3] Grace to you, and peace from God the Father, and our Lord Jesus Christ,
[1:4] who did give himself for our sins, that he might deliver us out of the present evil age, according to the will of God even our Father,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/1-genesis-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/1-genesis-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Genesis - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] In the beginning of God&amp;rsquo;s preparing the heavens and the earth &amp;ndash;
[1:2] the earth hath existed waste and void, and darkness `is&amp;rsquo; on the face of the deep, and the Spirit of God fluttering on the face of the waters,
[1:3] and God saith, `Let light be;&amp;rsquo; and light is.
[1:4] And God seeth the light that `it is&amp;rsquo; good, and God separateth between the light and the darkness,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habakkuk - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/35-habakkuk-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/35-habakkuk-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Habakkuk - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] The burden that Habakkuk the prophet hath seen:
[1:2] Till when, O Jehovah, have I cried, And Thou dost not hear? I cry unto Thee &amp;ndash; `Violence,&amp;rsquo; and Thou dost not save.
[1:3] Why dost Thou shew me iniquity, And perversity dost cause to behold? And spoiling and violence are&#39; before me, And there is strife, and contention doth lift itself&amp;rsquo; up,
[1:4] Therefore doth law cease, And judgment doth not go forth for ever, For the wicked is compassing the righteous, Therefore wrong judgment goeth forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haggai - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/37-haggai-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/37-haggai-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Haggai - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] In the second year of Darius the king, in the sixth month, in the first day of the month, hath a word of Jehovah been by the hand of Haggai the prophet, unto Zerubbabel son of Shealtiel, governor of Judah, and unto Joshua son of Josedech, the high priest, saying:
[1:2] Thus spake Jehovah of Hosts, saying: This people! &amp;ndash; they have said, The time hath not come, The time the house of Jehovah is&amp;rsquo; to be built.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hebrews - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/58-hebrews-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/58-hebrews-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Hebrews - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] In many parts, and many ways, God of old having spoken to the fathers in the prophets,
[1:2] in these last days did speak to us in a Son, whom He appointed heir of all things, through whom also He did make the ages;
[1:3] who being the brightness of the glory, and the impress of His subsistence, bearing up also the all things by the saying of his might &amp;ndash; through himself having made a cleansing of our sins, sat down at the right hand of the greatness in the highest,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/28-hosea-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/28-hosea-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Hosea - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A word of Jehovah that hath been unto Hosea, son of Beeri, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, Hezekiah, kings of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam son of Joash, king of Israel:
[1:2] The commencement of Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s speaking by Hosea. And Jehovah saith unto Hosea, `Go, take to thee a woman of whoredoms, and children of whoredoms, for utterly go a-whoring doth the land from after Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/23-isaiah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/23-isaiah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Isaiah - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] The Visions of Isaiah son of Amoz, that he hath seen concerning Judah and Jerusalem, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, Hezekiah, kings of Judah.
[1:2] Hear, O heavens, and give ear, O earth, For Jehovah hath spoken: Sons I have nourished and brought up, And they &amp;ndash; they transgressed against Me.
[1:3] An ox hath known its owner, And an ass the crib of its master, Israel hath not known, My people hath not understood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/59-james-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/59-james-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>James - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] James, of God and of the Lord Jesus Christ a servant, to the Twelve Tribes who are in the dispersion: Hail!
[1:2] All joy count `it&amp;rsquo;, my brethren, when ye may fall into temptations manifold;
[1:3] knowing that the proof of your faith doth work endurance,
[1:4] and let the endurance have a perfect work, that ye may be perfect and entire &amp;ndash; in nothing lacking;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/24-jeremiah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/24-jeremiah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Jeremiah - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Words of Jeremiah son of Hilkiah, of the priests who `are&amp;rsquo; in Anathoth, in the land of Benjamin,
[1:2] unto whom the word of Jehovah hath been in the days of Josiah son of Amon, king of Judah, in the thirteenth year of his reign,
[1:3] and it is in the days of Jehoiakim son of Josiah, king of Judah, till the completion of the eleventh year of Zedekiah son of Josiah, king of Judah, till the removal of Jerusalem in the fifth month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/18-job-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/18-job-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Job - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A man there hath been in the land of Uz &amp;ndash; Job his name &amp;ndash; and that man hath been perfect and upright &amp;ndash; both fearing God, and turning aside from evil.
[1:2] And there are borne to him seven sons and three daughters,
[1:3] and his substance is seven thousand sheep, and three thousand camels, and five hundred pairs of oxen, and five hundred she-asses, and a service very abundant; and that man is greater than any of the sons of the east.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/29-joel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/29-joel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Joel - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A word of Jehovah that hath been unto Joel, son of Pethuel:
[1:2] Hear this, ye aged ones, And give ear, all ye inhabitants of the land, Hath this been in your days? Or in the days of your fathers?
[1:3] Concerning it to your sons talk ye, And your sons to their sons, And their sons to another generation.
[1:4] What is left of the palmer-worm, eaten hath the locust, And what is left of the locust, Eaten hath the cankerworm, And what is left of the cankerworm, Eaten hath the caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/43-john-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/43-john-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>John - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] In the beginning was the Word, and the Word was with God, and the Word was God;
[1:2] this one was in the beginning with God;
[1:3] all things through him did happen, and without him happened not even one thing that hath happened.
[1:4] In him was life, and the life was the light of men,
[1:5] and the light in the darkness did shine, and the darkness did not perceive it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/32-jonah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/32-jonah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Jonah - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And there is a word of Jehovah unto Jonah son of Amittai, saying:
[1:2] `Rise, go unto Nineveh, the great city, and proclaim against it that their wickedness hath come up before Me.&amp;rsquo;
[1:3] And Jonah riseth to flee to Tarshish from the face of Jehovah, and goeth down to&#39; Joppa, and findeth a ship going to&amp;rsquo; Tarshish, and he giveth its fare, and goeth down into it, to go with them to Tarshish from the face of Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joshua - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/6-joshua-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/6-joshua-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Joshua - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And it cometh to pass after the death of Moses, servant of Jehovah, that Jehovah speaketh unto Joshua son of Nun, minister of Moses, saying,
[1:2] `Moses my servant is dead, and now, rise, pass over this Jordan, thou, and all this people, unto the land which I am giving to them, to the sons of Israel.
[1:3] `Every place on which the sole of your foot treadeth, to you I have given it, as I have spoken unto Moses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/65-jude-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/65-jude-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Jude - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Judas, of Jesus Christ a servant, and brother of James, to those sanctified in God the Father, and in Jesus Christ kept &amp;ndash; called,
[1:2] kindness to you, and peace, and love, be multiplied!
[1:3] Beloved, all diligence using to write to you concerning the common salvation, I had necessity to write to you, exhorting to agonize for the faith once delivered to the saints,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judges - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/7-judges-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/7-judges-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Judges - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And it cometh to pass, after the death of Joshua, that the sons of Israel ask at Jehovah, saying, `Who doth go up for us unto the Canaanite, at the commencement, to fight against it?&amp;rsquo;
[1:2] And Jehovah saith, `Judah doth go up; lo, I have given the land into his hand.&amp;rsquo;
[1:3] And Judah saith to Simeon his brother, `Go up with me into my lot, and we fight against the Canaanite &amp;ndash; and I have gone, even I, with thee into thy lot;&amp;rsquo; and Simeon goeth with him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamentations - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/25-lamentations-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/25-lamentations-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Lamentations - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] How hath she sat alone, The city abounding with people! She hath been as a widow, The mighty among nations! Princes among provinces, She hath become tributary!
[1:2] She weepeth sore in the night, And her tear `is&amp;rsquo; on her cheeks, There is no comforter for her out of all her lovers, All her friends dealt treacherously by her, They have been to her for enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/3-leviticus-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/3-leviticus-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Leviticus - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And Jehovah calleth unto Moses, and speaketh unto him out of the tent of meeting, saying,
[1:2] `Speak unto the sons of Israel, and thou hast said unto them, Any man of you when he doth bring near an offering to Jehovah, out of the cattle &amp;ndash; out of the herd, or out of the flock &amp;ndash; ye do bring near your offering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/42-luke-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/42-luke-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Luke - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Seeing that many did take in hand to set in order a narration of the matters that have been fully assured among us,
[1:2] as they did deliver to us, who from the beginning became eye-witnesses, and officers of the Word, &amp;ndash;
[1:3] it seemed good also to me, having followed from the first after all things exactly, to write to thee in order, most noble Theophilus,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malachi - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/39-malachi-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/39-malachi-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Malachi - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] The burden of a word of Jehovah unto Israel by the hand of Malachi:
[1:2] I have loved you, said Jehovah, And ye have said, `In what hast Thou loved us?&amp;rsquo;
[1:3] Is not Esau Jacob&amp;rsquo;s brother? &amp;ndash; an affirmation of Jehovah, And I love Jacob, and Esau I have hated, And I make his mountains a desolation, And his inheritance for dragons of a wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/41-mark-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/41-mark-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Mark - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A beginning of the good news of Jesus Christ, Son of God.
[1:2] As it hath been written in the prophets, `Lo, I send My messenger before thy face, who shall prepare thy way before thee,&amp;rsquo; &amp;ndash;
[1:3] `A voice of one calling in the wilderness, Prepare ye the way of the Lord, straight make ye his paths,&amp;rsquo; &amp;ndash;
[1:4] John came baptizing in the wilderness, and proclaiming a baptism of reformation &amp;ndash; to remission of sins,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/40-matthew-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/40-matthew-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Matthew - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A roll of the birth of Jesus Christ, son of David, son of Abraham.
[1:2] Abraham begat Isaac, and Isaac begat Jacob, and Jacob begat Judah and his brethren,
[1:3] and Judah begat Pharez and Zarah of Tamar, and Pharez begat Hezron, and Hezron begat Ram,
[1:4] and Ram begat Amminadab, and Amminadab begat Nahshon, and Nahshon begat Salmon,
[1:5] and Salmon begat Boaz of Rahab, and Boaz begat Obed of Ruth, and Obed begat Jesse,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/33-micah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/33-micah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Micah - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A word of Jehovah that hath been unto Micah the Morashite in the days of Jotham, Ahaz, Hezekiah, kings of Judah, that he hath seen concerning Samaria and Jerusalem:
[1:2] Hear, O peoples, all of them! Attend, O earth, and its fulness, And the Lord Jehovah is against you for a witness, The Lord from His holy temple.
[1:3] For lo, Jehovah is going out from His place, And He hath come down, And hath trodden on high places of earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nahum - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/34-nahum-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/34-nahum-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Nahum - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Burden of Nineveh. The Book of the Vision of Nahum the Elkoshite.
[1:2] A God zealous and avenging is&#39; Jehovah, An avenger is&amp;rsquo; Jehovah, and possessing fury. An avenger `is&amp;rsquo; Jehovah on His adversaries, And He is watching for His enemies.
[1:3] Jehovah is&#39; slow to anger, and great in power, And Jehovah doth not entirely acquit, In a hurricane and in a tempest is&amp;rsquo; His way, And a cloud `is&amp;rsquo; the dust of His feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nehemiah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/16-nehemiah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/16-nehemiah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Nehemiah - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Words of Nehemiah son of Hachaliah. And it cometh to pass, in the month of Chisleu, the twentieth year, and I have been in Shushan the palace,
[1:2] and come in doth Hanani, one of my brethren, he and men of Judah, and I ask them concerning the Jews, the escaped part that have been left of the captivity, and concerning Jerusalem;
[1:3] and they say to me, Those left, who have been left of the captivity there in the province, are&amp;rsquo; in great evil, and in reproach, and the wall of Jerusalem is broken down, and its gates have been burnt with fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numbers - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/4-numbers-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/4-numbers-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Numbers - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And Jehovah speaketh unto Moses in the wilderness of Sinai, in the tent of meeting, on the first of the second month, in the second year of their going out of the land of Egypt, saying:
[1:2] `Take ye up the sum of all the company of the sons of Israel by their families, by the house of their fathers, in the number of names &amp;ndash; every male by their polls;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obadiah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/31-obadiah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/31-obadiah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Obadiah - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Thus said the Lord Jehovah to Edom, A report we have heard from Jehovah, And an ambassador among nations was sent, `Rise, yea, let us rise against her for battle.&amp;rsquo;
[1:2] Lo, little I have made thee among nations, Despised `art&amp;rsquo; thou exceedingly.
[1:3] The pride of thy heart hath lifted thee up, O dweller in clifts of a rock, (A high place is&#39; his habitation, He is saying in his heart, Who doth bring me down `to&amp;rsquo; earth?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philemon - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/57-philemon-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/57-philemon-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Philemon - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, a prisoner of Christ Jesus, and Timotheus the brother, to Philemon our beloved and fellow-worker,
[1:2] and Apphia the beloved, and Archippus our fellow-soldier, and the assembly in thy house:
[1:3] Grace to you, and peace, from God our Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ!
[1:4] I give thanks to my God, always making mention of thee in my prayers,
[1:5] hearing of thy love and faith that thou hast unto the Lord Jesus and toward all the saints,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippians - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/50-philippians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/50-philippians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Philippians - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul and Timotheus, servants of Jesus Christ, to all the saints in Christ Jesus who are in Philippi, with overseers and ministrants;
[1:2] Grace to you, and peace from God our Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] I give thanks to my God upon all the remembrance of you,
[1:4] always, in every supplication of mine for you all, with joy making the supplication,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proverbs - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/20-proverbs-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/20-proverbs-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Proverbs - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Proverbs of Solomon, son of David, king of Israel:
[1:2] For knowing wisdom and instruction, For understanding sayings of intelligence,
[1:3] For receiving the instruction of wisdom, Righteousness, judgment, and uprightness,
[1:4] For giving to simple ones &amp;ndash; prudence, To a youth &amp;ndash; knowledge and discretion.
[1:5] (The wise doth hear and increaseth learning, And the intelligent doth obtain counsels.)
[1:6] For understanding a proverb and its sweetness, Words of the wise and their acute sayings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psalms - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/19-psalms-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/19-psalms-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Psalms - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] O the happiness of that one, who Hath not walked in the counsel of the wicked. And in the way of sinners hath not stood, And in the seat of scorners hath not sat;
[1:2] But &amp;ndash; in the law of Jehovah `is&amp;rsquo; his delight, And in His law he doth meditate by day and by night:
[1:3] And he hath been as a tree, Planted by rivulets of water, That giveth its fruit in its season, And its leaf doth not wither, And all that he doth he causeth to prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelation - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/66-revelation-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/66-revelation-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Revelation - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A revelation of Jesus Christ, that God gave to him, to shew to his servants what things it behoveth to come to pass quickly; and he did signify `it&amp;rsquo;, having sent through his messenger to his servant John,
[1:2] who did testify the word of God, and the testimony of Jesus Christ, as many things also as he did see.
[1:3] Happy is he who is reading, and those hearing, the words of the prophecy, and keeping the things written in it &amp;ndash; for the time is nigh!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romans - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/45-romans-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/45-romans-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Romans - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, a servant of Jesus Christ, a called apostle, having been separated to the good news of God &amp;ndash;
[1:2] which He announced before through His prophets in holy writings &amp;ndash;
[1:3] concerning His Son, (who is come of the seed of David according to the flesh,
[1:4] who is marked out Son of God in power, according to the Spirit of sanctification, by the rising again from the dead,) Jesus Christ our Lord;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruth - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/8-ruth-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/8-ruth-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Ruth - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And it cometh to pass, in the days of the judging of the judges, that there is a famine in the land, and there goeth a man from Beth-Lehem-Judah to sojourn in the fields of Moab, he, and his wife, and his two sons.
[1:2] And the name of the man `is&amp;rsquo; Elimelech, and the name of his wife Naomi, and the name of his two sons Mahlon and Chilion, Ephrathites from Beth-Lehem-Judah; and they come into the fields of Moab, and are there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song of Solomon - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/22-song-of-solomon-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/22-song-of-solomon-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Song of Solomon - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] The Song of Songs, that `is&amp;rsquo; Solomon&amp;rsquo;s.
[1:2] Let him kiss me with kisses of his mouth, For better `are&amp;rsquo; thy loves than wine.
[1:3] For fragrance `are&amp;rsquo; thy perfumes good. Perfume emptied out &amp;ndash; thy name, Therefore have virgins loved thee!
[1:4] Draw me: after thee we run, The king hath brought me into his inner chambers, We do joy and rejoice in thee, We mention thy loves more than wine, Uprightly they have loved thee!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Titus - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/56-titus-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/56-titus-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Titus - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] Paul, a servant of God, and an apostle of Jesus Christ, according to the faith of the choice ones of God, and an acknowledging of truth that `is&amp;rsquo; according to piety,
[1:2] upon hope of life age-during, which God, who doth not lie, did promise before times of ages,
[1:3] (and He manifested in proper times His word,) in preaching, which I was entrusted with, according to a charge of God our Saviour,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zechariah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/38-zechariah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/38-zechariah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Zechariah - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] In the eighth month, in the second year of Darius, hath a word of Jehovah been unto Zechariah, son of Berechiah, son of Iddo, the prophet, saying:
[1:2] `Jehovah was wroth against your fathers &amp;ndash; wrath!
[1:3] And thou hast said unto them, Thus said Jehovah of Hosts, turn back unto Me, An affirmation of Jehovah of Hosts, And I turn back unto you, said Jehovah of Hosts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephaniah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/36-zephaniah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/36-zephaniah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Zephaniah - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A word of Jehovah that hath been unto Zephaniah son of Cushi, son of Gedaliah, son of Amariah, son of Hezikiah, in the days of Josiah son of Amoz, king of Judah:
[1:2] I utterly consume all from off the face of the ground, An affirmation of Jehovah.
[1:3] I consume man and beast, I consume fowl of the heavens, and fishes of the sea, And the stumbling-blocks &amp;ndash; the wicked, And I have cut off man from the face of the ground, An affirmation of Jehovah,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>