<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3 John on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/3-john/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3 John on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/3-john/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3 John - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/64-3-john-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/64-3-john-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The elder unto Gaius the beloved, whom I love in truth.
[1:2] Beloved, I pray that in all things thou mayest prosper and be in health, even as thy soul prospereth.
[1:3] For I rejoiced greatly, when brethren came and bare witness unto thy truth, even as thou walkest in truth.
[1:4] Greater joy have I none than this, to hear of my children walking in the truth.
[1:5] Beloved, thou doest a faithful work in whatsoever thou doest toward them that are brethren and strangers withal;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 John - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/64-3-john-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/64-3-john-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] I, a ruler in the church, send word to the well loved Gaius, for whom I have true love.
[1:2] My loved one, it is my prayer that you may do well in all things, and be healthy in body, even as your soul does well.
[1:3] For it gave me great joy when some of the brothers came and gave witness that you had the true faith and were walking in the true way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 John - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/64-3-john-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/64-3-john-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The elder unto the wellbeloved Gaius, whom I love in the truth.
[1:2] Beloved, I wish above all things that thou mayest prosper and be in health, even as thy soul prospereth.
[1:3] For I rejoiced greatly, when the brethren came and testified of the truth that is in thee, even as thou walkest in the truth.
[1:4] I have no greater joy than to hear that my children walk in truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 John - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/64-3-john-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/64-3-john-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The elder to Gaius the beloved, whom I love in truth.
[1:2] Beloved, I pray that you may prosper in all things and be healthy, even as your soul prospers.
[1:3] For I rejoiced greatly, when brothers came and testified about your truth, even as you walk in truth.
[1:4] I have no greater joy than this, to hear about my children walking in truth.
[1:5] Beloved, you do a faithful work in whatever you accomplish for those who are brothers and strangers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 John - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/64-3-john-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/64-3-john-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Elder to Gaius the beloved, whom I love in truth!
[1:2] beloved, concerning all things I desire thee to prosper, and to be in health, even as thy soul doth prosper,
[1:3] for I rejoiced exceedingly, brethren coming and testifying of the truth in thee, even as thou in truth dost walk;
[1:4] greater than these things I have no joy, that I may hear of my children in truth walking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>