<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Revelation on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/revelation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Revelation on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/revelation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelation - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/66-revelation-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/66-revelation-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Revelation of Jesus Christ, which God gave him to show unto his servants, even&#39; the things which must shortly come to pass: and he sent and signified it&amp;rsquo; by his angel unto his servant John;
[1:2] who bare witness of the word of God, and of the testimony of Jesus Christ, `even&amp;rsquo; of all things that he saw.
[1:3] Blessed is he that readeth, and they that hear the words of the prophecy, and keep the things that are written therein: for the time is at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelation - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/66-revelation-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/66-revelation-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Revelation of Jesus Christ which God gave him so that his servants might have knowledge of the things which will quickly take place: and he sent and made it clear by his angel to his servant John;
[1:2] Who gave witness of the word of God, and of the witness of Jesus Christ, even of all the things which he saw.
[1:3] A blessing be on the reader, and on those who give ear to the prophet&amp;rsquo;s words, and keep the things which he has put in the book: for the time is near.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelation - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/66-revelation-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/66-revelation-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Revelation of Jesus Christ, which God gave unto him, to shew unto his servants things which must shortly come to pass; and he sent and signified it by his angel unto his servant John:
[1:2] Who bare record of the word of God, and of the testimony of Jesus Christ, and of all things that he saw.
[1:3] Blessed is he that readeth, and they that hear the words of this prophecy, and keep those things which are written therein: for the time is at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelation - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/66-revelation-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/66-revelation-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] This is the Revelation of Jesus Christ, which God gave him to show to his servants the things which must happen soon, which he sent and made known by his angel to his servant, John,
[1:2] who testified to God&amp;rsquo;s word, and of the testimony of Jesus Christ, about everything that he saw.
[1:3] Blessed is he who reads and those who hear the words of the prophecy, and keep the things that are written in it, for the time is at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelation - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/66-revelation-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/66-revelation-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] A revelation of Jesus Christ, that God gave to him, to shew to his servants what things it behoveth to come to pass quickly; and he did signify `it&amp;rsquo;, having sent through his messenger to his servant John,
[1:2] who did testify the word of God, and the testimony of Jesus Christ, as many things also as he did see.
[1:3] Happy is he who is reading, and those hearing, the words of the prophecy, and keeping the things written in it &amp;ndash; for the time is nigh!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>