<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ASV on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/asv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ASV on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/asv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Chronicles - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/13-1-chronicles-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/13-1-chronicles-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Adam, Seth, Enosh,
[1:2] Kenan, Mahalalel, Jared,
[1:3] Enoch, Methuselah, Lamech,
[1:4] Noah, Shem, Ham, and Japheth.
[1:5] The sons of Japheth: Gomer, and Magog, and Madai, and Javan, and Tubal, and Meshech, and Tiras.
[1:6] And the sons of Gomer: Ashkenaz, and Diphath, and Togarmah.
[1:7] And the sons of Javan: Elishah, and Tarshish, Kittim, and Rodanim.
[1:8] The sons of Ham: Cush, and Mizraim, Put, and Canaan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/46-1-corinthians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/46-1-corinthians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, called `to be&amp;rsquo; an apostle of Jesus Christ through the will of God, and Sosthenes our brother,
[1:2] unto the church of God which is at Corinth, even&#39; them that are sanctified in Christ Jesus, called to be&amp;rsquo; saints, with all that call upon the name of our Lord Jesus Christ in every place, their `Lord&amp;rsquo; and ours:
[1:3] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 John - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/62-1-john-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/62-1-john-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] That which was from the beginning, that which we have heard, that which we have seen with our eyes, that which we beheld, and our hands handled, concerning the Word of life
[1:2] (and the life was manifested, and we have seen, and bear witness, and declare unto you the life, the eternal `life&amp;rsquo;, which was with the Father, and was manifested unto us);
[1:3] that which we have seen and heard declare we unto you also, that ye also may have fellowship with us: yea, and our fellowship is with the Father, and with his Son Jesus Christ:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Kings - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/11-1-kings-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/11-1-kings-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now king David was old and stricken in years; and they covered him with clothes, but he gat no heat.
[1:2] Wherefore his servants said unto him, Let there be sought for my lord the king a young virgin: and let her stand before the king, and cherish him; and let her lie in thy bosom, that my lord the king may get heat.
[1:3] So they sought for a fair damsel throughout all the borders of Israel, and found Abishag the Shunammite, and brought her to the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Peter - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/60-1-peter-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/60-1-peter-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Peter, an apostle of Jesus Christ, to the elect who are sojourners of the Dispersion in Pontus, Galatia, Cappadocia, Asia, and Bithynia,
[1:2] according to the foreknowledge of God the Father, in sanctification of the Spirit, unto obedience and sprinkling of the blood of Jesus Christ: Grace to you and peace be multiplied.
[1:3] Blessed `be&amp;rsquo; the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who according to his great mercy begat us again unto a living hope by the resurrection of Jesus Christ from the dead,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Samuel - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/9-1-samuel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/9-1-samuel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now there was a certain man of Ramathaim-zophim, of the hill-country of Ephraim, and his name was Elkanah, the son of Jeroham, the son of Elihu, the son of Tohu, the son of Zuph, an Ephraimite:
[1:2] and he had two wives; the name of the one was Hannah, and the name of other Peninnah: and Peninnah had children, but Hannah had no children.
[1:3] And this man went up out of his city from year to year to worship and to sacrifice unto Jehovah of hosts in Shiloh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Thessalonians - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/52-1-thessalonians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/52-1-thessalonians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, and Silvanus, and Timothy, unto the church of the Thessalonians in God the Father and the Lord Jesus Christ: Grace to you and peace.
[1:2] We give thanks to God always for you all, making mention `of you&amp;rsquo; in our prayers;
[1:3] remembering without ceasing your work of faith and labor of love and patience of hope in our Lord Jesus Christ, before our God and Father;
[1:4] knowing, brethren beloved of God, your election,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Timothy - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/54-1-timothy-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/54-1-timothy-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Christ Jesus according to the commandment of God our Saviour, and Christ Jesus our hope;
[1:2] unto Timothy, my true child in faith: Grace, mercy, peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] As I exhorted thee to tarry at Ephesus, when I was going into Macedonia, that thou mightest charge certain men not to teach a different doctrine,
[1:4] neither to give heed to fables and endless genealogies, which minister questionings, rather than a dispensation of God which is in faith; `so do I now&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Chronicles - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/14-2-chronicles-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/14-2-chronicles-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And Solomon the son of David was strengthened in his kingdom, and Jehovah his God was with him, and magnified him exceedingly.
[1:2] And Solomon spake unto all Israel, to the captains of thousands and of hundreds, and to the judges, and to every prince in all Israel, the heads of the fathers&amp;rsquo; `houses&amp;rsquo;.
[1:3] So Solomon, and all the assembly with him, went to the high place that was at Gibeon; for there was the tent of meeting of God, which Moses the servant of Jehovah had made in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Corinthians - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/47-2-corinthians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/47-2-corinthians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Christ Jesus through the will of God, and Timothy our brother, unto the church of God which is at Corinth, with all the saints that are in the whole of Achaia:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] Blessed `be&amp;rsquo; the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, the Father of mercies and God of all comfort;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 John - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/63-2-john-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/63-2-john-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The elder unto the elect lady and her children, whom I love in truth; and not I only, but also all they that know the truth;
[1:2] for the truth&amp;rsquo;s sake which abideth in us, and it shall be with us for ever:
[1:3] Grace, mercy, peace shall be with us, from God the Father, and from Jesus Christ, the Son of the Father, in truth and love.
[1:4] I rejoice greatly that I have found `certain&amp;rsquo; of thy children walking in truth, even as we received commandment from the Father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/12-2-kings-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/12-2-kings-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And Moab rebelled against Israel after the death of Ahab.
[1:2] And Ahaziah fell down through the lattice in his upper chamber that was in Samaria, and was sick: and he sent messengers, and said unto them, Go, inquire of Baal-zebub, the god of Ekron, whether I shall recover of this sickness.
[1:3] But the angel of Jehovah said to Elijah the Tishbite, Arise, go up to meet the messengers of the king of Samaria, and say unto them, Is it because there is no God in Israel, that ye go to inquire of Baal-zebub, the god of Ekron?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Peter - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/61-2-peter-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/61-2-peter-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Simon Peter, a servant and apostle of Jesus Christ, to them that have obtained a like precious faith with us in the righteousness of our God and `the&amp;rsquo; Saviour Jesus Christ:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace be multiplied in the knowledge of God and of Jesus our Lord;
[1:3] seeing that his divine power hath granted unto us all things that pertain unto life and godliness, through the knowledge of him that called us by his own glory and virtue;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Samuel - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/10-2-samuel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/10-2-samuel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And it came to pass after the death of Saul, when David was returned from the slaughter of the Amalekites, and David had abode two days in Ziklag;
[1:2] it came to pass on the third day, that, behold, a man came out of the camp from Saul, with his clothes rent, and earth upon his head: and so it was, when he came to David, that he fell to the earth, and did obeisance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Thessalonians - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/53-2-thessalonians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/53-2-thessalonians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, and Silvanus, and Timothy, unto the church of the Thessalonians in God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ;
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God the Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] We are bound to give thanks to God always to you, brethren, even as it is meet, for that your faith growth exceedingly, and the love of each one of you all toward one another aboundeth;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Timothy - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/55-2-timothy-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/55-2-timothy-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Christ Jesus through the will of God, according to the promise of the life which is in Christ Jesus,
[1:2] to Timothy, my beloved child: Grace, mercy, peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] I thank God, whom I serve from my forefathers in a pure conscience, how unceasing is my remembrance of thee in my supplications, night and day
[1:4] longing to see thee, remembering thy tears, that I may be filled with joy;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 John - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/64-3-john-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/64-3-john-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The elder unto Gaius the beloved, whom I love in truth.
[1:2] Beloved, I pray that in all things thou mayest prosper and be in health, even as thy soul prospereth.
[1:3] For I rejoiced greatly, when brethren came and bare witness unto thy truth, even as thou walkest in truth.
[1:4] Greater joy have I none than this, to hear of my children walking in the truth.
[1:5] Beloved, thou doest a faithful work in whatsoever thou doest toward them that are brethren and strangers withal;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acts - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/44-acts-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/44-acts-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The former treatise I made, O Theophilus, concerning all that Jesus began both to do and to teach,
[1:2] until the day in which he was received up, after that he had given commandment through the Holy Spirit unto the apostles whom he had chosen:
[1:3] To whom he also showed himself alive after his passion by many proofs, appearing unto them by the space of forty days, and speaking the things concerning the kingdom of God:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amos - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/30-amos-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/30-amos-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The words of Amos, who was among the herdsmen of Tekoa, which he saw concerning Israel in the days of Uzziah king of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam the son of Joash king of Israel, two years before the earthquake.
[1:2] And he said, Jehovah will roar from Zion, and utter his voice from Jerusalem; and the pastures of the shepherds shall mourn, and the top of Carmel shall wither.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colossians - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/51-colossians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/51-colossians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Christ Jesus through the will of God, and Timothy our brother,
[1:2] To the saints and faithful brethren in Christ `that are&amp;rsquo; at Colossae: Grace to you and peace from God our Father.
[1:3] We give thanks to God the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, praying always for you,
[1:4] having heard of your faith in Christ Jesus, and of the love which ye have toward all the saints,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/27-daniel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/27-daniel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the third year of the reign of Jehoiakim king of Judah came Nebuchadnezzar king of Babylon unto Jerusalem, and besieged it.
[1:2] And the Lord gave Jehoiakim king of Judah into his hand, with part of the vessels of the house of God; and he carried them into the land of Shinar to the house of his god: and he brought the vessels into the treasure-house of his god.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/5-deuteronomy-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/5-deuteronomy-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] These are the words which Moses spake unto all Israel beyond the Jordan in the wilderness, in the Arabah over against Suph, between Paran, and Tophel, and Laban, and Hazeroth, and Di-zahab.
[1:2] It is eleven days&amp;rsquo; `journey&amp;rsquo; from Horeb by the way of mount Seir unto Kadesh-barnea.
[1:3] And it came to pass in the fortieth year, in the eleventh month, on the first day of the month, that Moses spake unto the children of Israel, according unto all that Jehovah had given him in commandment unto them;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecclesiastes - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/21-ecclesiastes-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/21-ecclesiastes-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The words of the Preacher, the son of David, king in Jerusalem.
[1:2] Vanity of vanities, saith the Preacher; vanity of vanities, all is vanity.
[1:3] What profit hath man of all his labor wherein he laboreth under the sun?
[1:4] One generation goeth, and another generation cometh; but the earth abideth for ever.
[1:5] The sun also ariseth, and the sun goeth down, and hasteth to its place where it ariseth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ephesians - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/49-ephesians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/49-ephesians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Christ Jesus through the will of God, to the saints that are at Ephesus, and the faithful in Christ Jesus:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] Blessed be&#39; the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who hath blessed us with every spiritual blessing in the heavenly places&amp;rsquo; in Christ:
[1:4] even as he chose us in him before the foundation of the world, that we should be holy and without blemish before him in love:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/17-esther-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/17-esther-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came to pass in the days of Ahasuerus (this is Ahasuerus who reigned from India even unto Ethiopia, over a hundred and seven and twenty provinces),
[1:2] that in those days, when the king Ahasuerus sat on the throne of his kingdom, which was in Shushan the palace,
[1:3] in the third year of his reign, he made a feast unto all his princes and his servants; the power of Persia and Media, the nobles and princes of the provinces, being before him;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exodus - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/2-exodus-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/2-exodus-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now these are the names of the sons of Israel, who came into Egypt (every man and his household came with Jacob):
[1:2] Reuben, Simeon, Levi, and Judah,
[1:3] Issachar, Zebulun, and Benjamin,
[1:4] Dan and Naphtali, Gad and Asher.
[1:5] And all the souls that came out of the loins of Jacob were seventy souls: and Joseph was in Egypt already.
[1:6] And Joseph died, and all his brethren, and all that generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/26-ezekiel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/26-ezekiel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came to pass in the thirtieth year, in the fourth month&#39;, in the fifth day&amp;rsquo; of the month, as I was among the captives by the river Chebar, that the heavens were opened, and I saw visions of God.
[1:2] In the fifth `day&amp;rsquo; of the month, which was the fifth year of king Jehoiachin&amp;rsquo;s captivity,
[1:3] the word of Jehovah came expressly unto Ezekiel the priest, the son of Buzi, in the land of the Chaldeans by the river Chebar; and the hand of Jehovah was there upon him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezra - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/15-ezra-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/15-ezra-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now in the first year of Cyrus king of Persia, that the word of Jehovah by the mouth of Jeremiah might be accomplished, Jehovah stirred up the spirit of Cyrus king of Persia, so that he made a proclamation throughout all his kingdom, and `put it&amp;rsquo; also in writing, saying,
[1:2] Thus saith Cyrus king of Persia, All the kingdoms of the earth hath Jehovah, the God of heaven, given me; and he hath charged me to build him a house in Jerusalem, which is in Judah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galatians - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/48-galatians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/48-galatians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle (not from men, neither through man, but through Jesus Christ, and God the Father, who raised him from the dead),
[1:2] and all the brethren that are with me, unto the churches of Galatia:
[1:3] Grace to you and peace from God the Father, and our Lord Jesus Christ,
[1:4] who gave himself for our sins, that he might deliver us out of this present evil world, according to the will of our God and Father:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/1-genesis-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/1-genesis-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the beginning God created the heavens and the earth.
[1:2] And the earth was waste and void; and darkness was upon the face of the deep: and the Spirit of God moved upon the face of the waters.
[1:3] And God said, Let there be light: and there was light.
[1:4] And God saw the light, that it was good: and God divided the light from the darkness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habakkuk - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/35-habakkuk-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/35-habakkuk-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden which Habakkuk the prophet did see.
[1:2] O Jehovah, how long shall I cry, and thou wilt not hear? I cry out unto thee of violence, and thou wilt not save.
[1:3] Why dost thou show me iniquity, and look upon perverseness? for destruction and violence are before me; and there is strife, and contention riseth up.
[1:4] Therefore the law is slacked, and justice doth never go forth; for the wicked doth compass about the righteous; therefore justice goeth forth perverted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haggai - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/37-haggai-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/37-haggai-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the second year of Darius the king, in the sixth month, in the first day of the month, came the word of Jehovah by Haggai the prophet unto Zerubbabel the son of Shealtiel, governor of Judah, and to Joshua the son of Jehozadak, the high priest, saying,
[1:2] Thus speaketh Jehovah of hosts, saying, This people say, It is not the time `for us&amp;rsquo; to come, the time for Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s house to be built.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hebrews - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/58-hebrews-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/58-hebrews-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] God, having of old time spoken unto the fathers in the prophets by divers portions and in divers manners,
[1:2] hath at the end of these days spoken unto us in `his&amp;rsquo; Son, whom he appointed heir of all things, through whom also he made the worlds;
[1:3] who being the effulgence of his glory, and the very image of his substance, and upholding all things by the word of his power, when he had made purification of sins, sat down on the right hand of the Majesty on high;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/28-hosea-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/28-hosea-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of Jehovah that came unto Hosea the son of Beeri, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam the son of Joash, king of Israel.
[1:2] When Jehovah spake at the first by Hosea, Jehovah said unto Hosea, Go, take unto thee a wife of whoredom and children of whoredom; for the land doth commit great whoredom, `departing&amp;rsquo; from Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/23-isaiah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/23-isaiah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The vision of Isaiah the son of Amoz, which he saw concerning Judah and Jerusalem, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah.
[1:2] Hear, O heavens, and give ear, O earth; for Jehovah hath spoken: I have nourished and brought up children, and they have rebelled against me.
[1:3] The ox knoweth his owner, and the ass his master&amp;rsquo;s crib; `but&amp;rsquo; Israel doth not know, my people doth not consider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/59-james-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/59-james-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] James, a servant of God and of the Lord Jesus Christ, to the twelve tribes which are of the Dispersion, greeting.
[1:2] Count it all joy, my brethren, when ye fall into manifold temptations;
[1:3] Knowing that the proving of your faith worketh patience.
[1:4] And let patience have `its&amp;rsquo; perfect work, that ye may be perfect and entire, lacking in nothing.
[1:5] But if any of you lacketh wisdom, let him ask of God, who giveth to all liberally and upbraideth not; and it shall be given him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/24-jeremiah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/24-jeremiah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The words of Jeremiah the son of Hilkiah, of the priests that were in Anathoth in the land of Benjamin:
[1:2] to whom the word of Jehovah came in the days of Josiah the son of Amon, king of Judah, in the thirteenth year of his reign.
[1:3] It came also in the days of Jehoiakim the son of Josiah, king of Judah, unto the end of the eleventh year of Zedekiah, the son of Josiah, king of Judah, unto the carrying away of Jerusalem captive in the fifth month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/18-job-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/18-job-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] There was a man in the land of Uz, whose name was Job; and that man was perfect and upright, and one that feared God, and turned away from evil.
[1:2] And there were born unto him seven sons and three daughters.
[1:3] His substance also was seven thousand sheep, and three thousand camels, and five hundred yoke of oxen, and five hundred she-asses, and a very great household; so that this man was the greatest of all the children of the east.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/29-joel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/29-joel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of Jehovah that came to Joel the son of Pethuel.
[1:2] Hear this, ye old men, and give ear, all ye inhabitants of the land. Hath this been in your days, or in the days of your fathers?
[1:3] Tell ye your children of it, and let&#39; your children tell&amp;rsquo; their children, and their children another generation.
[1:4] That which the palmer-worm hath left hath the locust eaten; and that which the locust hath left hath the canker-worm eaten; and that which the canker-worm hath left hath the caterpillar eaten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/43-john-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/43-john-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the beginning was the Word, and the Word was with God, and the Word was God.
[1:2] The same was in the beginning with God.
[1:3] All things were made through him; and without him was not anything made that hath been made.
[1:4] In him was life; and the life was the light of men.
[1:5] And the light shineth in the darkness; and the darkness apprehended it not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/32-jonah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/32-jonah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now the word of Jehovah came unto Jonah the son of Amittai, saying,
[1:2] Arise, go to Nineveh, that great city, and cry against it; for their wickedness is come up before me.
[1:3] But Jonah rose up to flee unto Tarshish from the presence of Jehovah; and he went down to Joppa, and found a ship going to Tarshish: so he paid the fare thereof, and went down into it, to go with them unto Tarshish from the presence of Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joshua - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/6-joshua-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/6-joshua-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came to pass after the death of Moses the servant of Jehovah, that Jehovah spake unto Joshua the son of Nun, Moses&amp;rsquo; minister, saying,
[1:2] Moses my servant is dead; now therefore arise, go over this Jordan, thou, and all this people, unto the land which I do give to them, even to the children of Israel.
[1:3] Every place that the sole of your foot shall tread upon, to you have I given it, as I spake unto Moses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/65-jude-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/65-jude-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Jude, a servant of Jesus Christ, and brother of James, to them that are called, beloved in God the Father, and kept for Jesus Christ:
[1:2] Mercy unto you and peace and love be multiplied.
[1:3] Beloved, while I was giving all diligence to write unto you of our common salvation, I was constrained to write unto you exhorting you to contend earnestly for the faith which was once for all delivered unto the saints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judges - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/7-judges-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/7-judges-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And it came to pass after the death of Joshua, that the children of Israel asked of Jehovah, saying, Who shall go up for us first against the Canaanites, to fight against them?
[1:2] And Jehovah said, Judah shall go up: behold, I have delivered the land into his hand.
[1:3] And Judah said unto Simeon his brother, Come up with me into my lot, that we may fight against the Canaanites; and I likewise will go with thee into thy lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamentations - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/25-lamentations-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/25-lamentations-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] How doth the city sit solitary, that was full of people! She is become as a widow, that was great among the nations! She that was a princess among the provinces is become tributary!
[1:2] She weepeth sore in the night, and her tears are on her cheeks; Among all her lovers she hath none to comfort her: All her friends have dealt treacherously with her; they are become her enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/3-leviticus-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/3-leviticus-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And Jehovah called unto Moses, and spake unto him out of the tent of meeting, saying,
[1:2] Speak unto the children of Israel, and say unto them, When any man of you offereth an oblation unto Jehovah, ye shall offer your oblation of the cattle, `even&amp;rsquo; of the herd and of the flock.
[1:3] If his oblation be a burnt-offering of the herd, he shall offer it a male without blemish: he shall offer it at the door of the tent of meeting, that he may be accepted before Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/42-luke-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/42-luke-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Forasmuch as many have taken in hand to draw up a narrative concerning those matters which have been fulfilled among us,
[1:2] even as they delivered them unto us, who from the beginning wer eyewitnesses and ministers of the word,
[1:3] it seemed good to me also, having traced the course of all things accurately from the first, to write unto thee in order, most excellent Theophilus;
[1:4] that thou mightest know the certainty concerning the things wherein thou wast instructed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malachi - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/39-malachi-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/39-malachi-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden of the word of Jehovah to Israel by Malachi.
[1:2] I have loved you, saith Jehovah. Yet ye say, Wherein hast thou loved us? Was not Esau Jacob&amp;rsquo;s brother, saith Jehovah: yet I loved Jacob;
[1:3] but Esau I hated, and made his mountains a desolation, and `gave&amp;rsquo; his heritage to the jackals of the wilderness.
[1:4] Whereas Edom saith, We are beaten down, but we will return and build the waste places; thus saith Jehovah of hosts, They shall build, but I will throw down; and men shall call them The border of wickedness, and The people against whom Jehovah hath indignation for ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/41-mark-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/41-mark-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The beginning of the gospel of Jesus Christ, the Son of God.
[1:2] Even as it is written in Isaiah the prophet, Behold, I send my messenger before thy face, Who shall prepare thy way.
[1:3] The voice of one crying in the wilderness, Make ye ready the way of the Lord, Make his paths straight;
[1:4] John came, who baptized in the wilderness and preached the baptism of repentance unto remission of sins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/40-matthew-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/40-matthew-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The book of the generation of Jesus Christ, the son of David, the son of Abraham.
[1:2] Abraham begat Isaac; and Isaac begat Jacob; and Jacob begat Judah and his brethren;
[1:3] and Judah begat Perez and Zerah of Tamar; and Perez begat Hezron; and Hezron begat Ram;
[1:4] and Ram begat Amminadab; and Amminadab begat Nahshon; and Nahshon begat Salmon;
[1:5] and Salmon begat Boaz of Rahab; and Boaz begat Obed of Ruth; and Obed begat Jesse;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/33-micah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/33-micah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of Jehovah that came to Micah the Morashtite in the days of Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, which he saw concerning Samaria and Jerusalem.
[1:2] Hear, ye peoples, all of you: hearken, O earth, and all that therein is: and let the Lord Jehovah be witness against you, the Lord from his holy temple.
[1:3] For, behold, Jehovah cometh forth out of his place, and will come down, and tread upon the high places of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nahum - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/34-nahum-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/34-nahum-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden of Nineveh. The book of the vision of Nahum the Elkoshite.
[1:2] Jehovah is a jealous God and avengeth; Jehovah avengeth and is full of wrath; Jehovah taketh vengeance on his adversaries, and he reserveth `wrath&amp;rsquo; for his enemies.
[1:3] Jehovah is slow to anger, and great in power, and will by no means clear `the guilty&amp;rsquo;: Jehovah hath his way in the whirlwind and in the storm, and the clouds are the dust of his feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nehemiah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/16-nehemiah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/16-nehemiah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The words of Nehemiah the son of Hacaliah. Now it came to pass in the month Chislev, in the twentieth year, as I was in Shushan the palace,
[1:2] that Hanani, one of my brethren, came, he and certain men out of Judah; and I asked them concerning the Jews that had escaped, that were left of the captivity, and concerning Jerusalem.
[1:3] And they said unto me, The remnant that are left of the captivity there in the province are in great affliction and reproach: the wall of Jerusalem also is broken down, and the gates thereof are burned with fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numbers - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/4-numbers-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/4-numbers-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And Jehovah spake unto Moses in the wilderness of Sinai, in the tent of meeting, on the first day of the second month, in the second year after they were come out of the land of Egypt, saying,
[1:2] Take ye the sum of all the congregation of the children of Israel, by their families, by their fathers&amp;rsquo; houses, according to the number of the names, every male, by their polls;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obadiah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/31-obadiah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/31-obadiah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The vision of Obadiah. Thus saith the Lord Jehovah concerning Edom: We have heard tidings from Jehovah, and an ambassador is sent among the nations, `saying&amp;rsquo;, Arise ye, and let us rise up against her in battle.
[1:2] Behold, I have made thee small among the nations: thou art greatly despised.
[1:3] The pride of thy heart hath deceived thee, O thou that dwellest in the clefts of the rock, whose habitation is high; that saith in his heart, Who shall bring me down to the ground?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philemon - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/57-philemon-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/57-philemon-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, a prisoner of Christ Jesus, and Timothy our brother, to Philemon our beloved and fellow-worker,
[1:2] and to Apphia our sister, and to Archippus our fellow-soldier, and to the church in thy house:
[1:3] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:4] I thank my God always, making mention of thee in my prayers,
[1:5] hearing of thy love, and of the faith which thou hast toward the Lord Jesus, and toward all the saints;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippians - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/50-philippians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/50-philippians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul and Timothy, servants of Christ Jesus, to all the saints in Christ Jesus that are at Philippi, with the bishops and deacons:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] I thank my God upon all my remembrance of you,
[1:4] always in every supplication of mine on behalf of you all making my supplication with joy,
[1:5] for your fellowship in furtherance of the gospel from the first day until now;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proverbs - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/20-proverbs-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/20-proverbs-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The proverbs of Solomon the son of David, king of Israel:
[1:2] To know wisdom and instruction; To discern the words of understanding;
[1:3] To receive instruction in wise dealing, In righteousness and justice and equity;
[1:4] To give prudence to the simple, To the young man knowledge and discretion:
[1:5] That the wise man may hear, and increase in learning; And that the man of understanding may attain unto sound counsels:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psalms - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/19-psalms-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/19-psalms-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Blessed is the man that walketh not in the counsel of the wicked, Nor standeth in the way of sinners, Nor sitteth in the seat of scoffers:
[1:2] But his delight is in the law of Jehovah; And on his law doth he meditate day and night.
[1:3] And he shall be like a tree planted by the streams of water, That bringeth forth its fruit in its season, Whose leaf also doth not wither; And whatsoever he doeth shall prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelation - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/66-revelation-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/66-revelation-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Revelation of Jesus Christ, which God gave him to show unto his servants, even&#39; the things which must shortly come to pass: and he sent and signified it&amp;rsquo; by his angel unto his servant John;
[1:2] who bare witness of the word of God, and of the testimony of Jesus Christ, `even&amp;rsquo; of all things that he saw.
[1:3] Blessed is he that readeth, and they that hear the words of the prophecy, and keep the things that are written therein: for the time is at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romans - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/45-romans-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/45-romans-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, a servant of Jesus Christ, called `to be&amp;rsquo; an apostle, separated unto the gospel of God,
[1:2] which he promised afore through his prophets in the holy scriptures,
[1:3] concerning his Son, who was born of the seed of David according to the flesh,
[1:4] who was declared to be&#39; the Son of God with power, according to the spirit of holiness, by the resurrection from the dead; even&amp;rsquo; Jesus Christ our Lord,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruth - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/8-ruth-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/8-ruth-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And it came to pass in the days when the judges judged, that there was a famine in the land. And a certain man of Bethlehem-judah went to sojourn in the country of Moab, he, and his wife, and his two sons.
[1:2] And the name of the man was Elimelech, and the name of his wife Naomi, and the name of his two sons Mahlon and Chilion, Ephrathites of Bethlehem-judah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song of Solomon - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/22-song-of-solomon-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/22-song-of-solomon-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Song of songs, which is Solomon&amp;rsquo;s.
[1:2] Let him kiss me with the kisses of his mouth; For thy love is better than wine.
[1:3] Thine oils have a goodly fragrance; Thy name is `as&amp;rsquo; oil poured forth; Therefore do the virgins love thee.
[1:4] Draw me; we will run after thee: The king hath brought me into his chambers; We will be glad and rejoice in thee; We will make mention of thy love more than of wine: Rightly do they love thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Titus - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/56-titus-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/56-titus-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, a servant of God, and an apostle of Jesus Christ, according to the faith of God&amp;rsquo;s elect, and the knowledge of the truth which is according to godliness,
[1:2] in hope of eternal life, which God, who cannot lie, promised before times eternal;
[1:3] but in his own seasons manifested his word in the message, wherewith I was intrusted according to the commandment of God our Saviour;
[1:4] to Titus, my true child after a common faith: Grace and peace from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Saviour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zechariah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/38-zechariah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/38-zechariah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the eighth month, in the second year of Darius, came the word of Jehovah unto Zechariah the son of Berechiah, the son of Iddo, the prophet, saying,
[1:2] Jehovah was sore displeased with your fathers.
[1:3] Therefore say thou unto them, Thus saith Jehovah of hosts: Return unto me, saith Jehovah of hosts, and I will return unto you, saith Jehovah of hosts.
[1:4] Be ye not as your fathers, unto whom the former prophets cried, saying, Thus saith Jehovah of hosts, Return ye now from your evil ways, and from your evil doings: but they did not hear, nor hearken unto me, saith Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephaniah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/36-zephaniah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/36-zephaniah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of Jehovah which came unto Zephaniah the son of Cushi, the son of Gedaliah, the son of Amariah, the son of Hezekiah, in the days of Josiah the son of Amon, king of Judah.
[1:2] I will utterly consume all things from off the face of the ground, saith Jehovah.
[1:3] I will consume man and beast; I will consume the birds of the heavens, and the fishes of the sea, and the stumblingblocks with the wicked; and I will cut off man from off the face of the ground, saith Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>