<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 Kings on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/1-kings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 Kings on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/1-kings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Kings - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/11-1-kings-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/11-1-kings-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now king David was old and stricken in years; and they covered him with clothes, but he gat no heat.
[1:2] Wherefore his servants said unto him, Let there be sought for my lord the king a young virgin: and let her stand before the king, and cherish him; and let her lie in thy bosom, that my lord the king may get heat.
[1:3] So they sought for a fair damsel throughout all the borders of Israel, and found Abishag the Shunammite, and brought her to the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Kings - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/11-1-kings-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/11-1-kings-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now King David was old and far on in years; and though they put covers over him, his body was cold.
[1:2] So his servants said to him, Let search be made for a young virgin for my lord the king, to take care of him and be waiting on him; and you may take her in your arms, and so my lord the king will be warm.
[1:3] So after searching through all the land of Israel for a fair young girl, they saw Abishag the Shunammite, and took her to the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Kings - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/11-1-kings-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/11-1-kings-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now king David was old and stricken in years; and they covered him with clothes, but he gat no heat.
[1:2] Wherefore his servants said unto him, Let there be sought for my lord the king a young virgin: and let her stand before the king, and let her cherish him, and let her lie in thy bosom, that my lord the king may get heat.
[1:3] So they sought for a fair damsel throughout all the coasts of Israel, and found Abishag a Shunammite, and brought her to the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Kings - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/11-1-kings-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/11-1-kings-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now king David was old and stricken in years; and they covered him with clothes, but he got no heat.
[1:2] Therefore his servants said to him, Let there be sought for my lord the king a young virgin: and let her stand before the king, and cherish him; and let her lie in your bosom, that my lord the king may keep warm.
[1:3] So they sought for a beautiful young lady throughout all the borders of Israel, and found Abishag the Shunammite, and brought her to the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Kings - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/11-1-kings-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/11-1-kings-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And king David `is&amp;rsquo; old, entering into days, and they cover him with garments, and he hath no heat,
[1:2] and his servants say to him, `Let them seek for my lord the king a young woman, a virgin, and she hath stood before the king, and is to him a companion, and hath lain in thy bosom, and my lord the king hath heat.&amp;rsquo;
[1:3] And they seek a fair young woman in all the border of Israel, and find Abishag the Shunammite, and bring her in to the king,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>