<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Malachi on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/malachi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Malachi on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/malachi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Malachi - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/39-malachi-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/39-malachi-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden of the word of Jehovah to Israel by Malachi.
[1:2] I have loved you, saith Jehovah. Yet ye say, Wherein hast thou loved us? Was not Esau Jacob&amp;rsquo;s brother, saith Jehovah: yet I loved Jacob;
[1:3] but Esau I hated, and made his mountains a desolation, and `gave&amp;rsquo; his heritage to the jackals of the wilderness.
[1:4] Whereas Edom saith, We are beaten down, but we will return and build the waste places; thus saith Jehovah of hosts, They shall build, but I will throw down; and men shall call them The border of wickedness, and The people against whom Jehovah hath indignation for ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malachi - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/39-malachi-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/39-malachi-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of the Lord to Israel by Malachi.
[1:2] You have been loved by me, says the Lord. But you say, Where was your love for us? Was not Esau Jacob&amp;rsquo;s brother? says the Lord: but Jacob was loved by me,
[1:3] And Esau was hated, and I sent destruction on his mountains, and gave his heritage to the beasts of the waste land.
[1:4] Though Edom says, We are crushed down but we will come back, building up the waste places; this is what the Lord of armies has said: They may put up buildings, but I will have them pulled down; and they will be named The land of evil-doing, and The people against whom the Lord keeps his wrath for ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malachi - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/39-malachi-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/39-malachi-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden of the word of the LORD to Israel by Malachi.
[1:2] I have loved you, saith the LORD. Yet ye say, Wherein hast thou loved us? Was not Esau Jacob&amp;rsquo;s brother? saith the LORD: yet I loved Jacob,
[1:3] And I hated Esau, and laid his mountains and his heritage waste for the dragons of the wilderness.
[1:4] Whereas Edom saith, We are impoverished, but we will return and build the desolate places; thus saith the LORD of hosts, They shall build, but I will throw down; and they shall call them, The border of wickedness, and, The people against whom the LORD hath indignation for ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malachi - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/39-malachi-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/39-malachi-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] An oracle: the word of Yahweh to Israel by Malachi.
[1:2] &amp;ldquo;I have loved you,&amp;rdquo; says Yahweh. Yet you say, &amp;ldquo;How have you loved us?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Wasn&amp;rsquo;t Esau Jacob&amp;rsquo;s brother?&amp;rdquo; says Yahweh, &amp;ldquo;Yet I loved Jacob;
[1:3] but Esau I hated, and made his mountains a desolation, and gave his heritage to the jackals of the wilderness.&amp;rdquo;
[1:4] Whereas Edom says, &amp;ldquo;We are beaten down, but we will return and build the waste places;&amp;rdquo; thus says Yahweh of Hosts, &amp;ldquo;They shall build, but I will throw down; and men will call them &amp;lsquo;The Wicked Land,&amp;rsquo; even the people against whom Yahweh shows wrath forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malachi - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/39-malachi-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/39-malachi-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden of a word of Jehovah unto Israel by the hand of Malachi:
[1:2] I have loved you, said Jehovah, And ye have said, `In what hast Thou loved us?&amp;rsquo;
[1:3] Is not Esau Jacob&amp;rsquo;s brother? &amp;ndash; an affirmation of Jehovah, And I love Jacob, and Esau I have hated, And I make his mountains a desolation, And his inheritance for dragons of a wilderness.
[1:4] Because Edom saith, We have been made poor, And we turn back and we build the wastes,&#39; Thus said Jehovah of Hosts: They do build, and I do destroy, And men&amp;rsquo; have called to them, O region of wickedness,&#39; O people whom Jehovah defied to the age.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>