<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zephaniah on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/zephaniah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zephaniah on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/zephaniah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephaniah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/36-zephaniah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/36-zephaniah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of Jehovah which came unto Zephaniah the son of Cushi, the son of Gedaliah, the son of Amariah, the son of Hezekiah, in the days of Josiah the son of Amon, king of Judah.
[1:2] I will utterly consume all things from off the face of the ground, saith Jehovah.
[1:3] I will consume man and beast; I will consume the birds of the heavens, and the fishes of the sea, and the stumblingblocks with the wicked; and I will cut off man from off the face of the ground, saith Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephaniah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/36-zephaniah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/36-zephaniah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of the Lord which came to Zephaniah, the son of Cushi, the son of Gedaliah, the son of Amariah, the son of Hezekiah, in the days of Josiah, the son of Amon, king of Judah.
[1:2] I will take away everything from the face of the earth, says the Lord.
[1:3] I will take away man and beast; I will take away the birds of the heaven and the fishes of the sea; causing the downfall of the evil-doers, and cutting man off from the face of the earth, says the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephaniah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/36-zephaniah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/36-zephaniah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of the LORD which came unto Zephaniah the son of Cushi, the son of Gedaliah, the son of Amariah, the son of Hizkiah, in the days of Josiah the son of Amon, king of Judah.
[1:2] I will utterly consume all things from off the land, saith the LORD.
[1:3] I will consume man and beast; I will consume the fowls of the heaven, and the fishes of the sea, and the stumblingblocks with the wicked: and I will cut off man from off the land, saith the LORD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephaniah - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/36-zephaniah-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/36-zephaniah-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of Yahweh which came to Zephaniah, the son of Cushi, the son of Gedaliah, the son of Amariah, the son of Hezekiah, in the days of Josiah, the son of Amon, king of Judah.
[1:2] I will utterly sweep away everything off of the surface of the earth, says Yahweh.
[1:3] I will sweep away man and animal. I will sweep away the birds of the sky, the fish of the sea, and the heaps of rubble with the wicked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephaniah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/36-zephaniah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/36-zephaniah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] A word of Jehovah that hath been unto Zephaniah son of Cushi, son of Gedaliah, son of Amariah, son of Hezikiah, in the days of Josiah son of Amoz, king of Judah:
[1:2] I utterly consume all from off the face of the ground, An affirmation of Jehovah.
[1:3] I consume man and beast, I consume fowl of the heavens, and fishes of the sea, And the stumbling-blocks &amp;ndash; the wicked, And I have cut off man from the face of the ground, An affirmation of Jehovah,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>