<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 Kings on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/2-kings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 Kings on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/2-kings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/12-2-kings-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/12-2-kings-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>2 Kings - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV) [1:1] And Moab rebelled against Israel after the death of Ahab.
[1:2] And Ahaziah fell down through the lattice in his upper chamber that was in Samaria, and was sick: and he sent messengers, and said unto them, Go, inquire of Baal-zebub, the god of Ekron, whether I shall recover of this sickness.
[1:3] But the angel of Jehovah said to Elijah the Tishbite, Arise, go up to meet the messengers of the king of Samaria, and say unto them, Is it because there is no God in Israel, that ye go to inquire of Baal-zebub, the god of Ekron?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/12-2-kings-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/12-2-kings-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>2 Kings - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] After the death of Ahab, Moab made itself free from the authority of Israel.
[1:2] Now Ahaziah had a fall from the window of his room in Samaria, and was ill. And he sent men, and said to them, Put a question to Baal-zebub, the god of Ekron, about the outcome of my disease, to see if I will get well or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/12-2-kings-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/12-2-kings-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>2 Kings - King James Version (KJV) [1:1] Then Moab rebelled against Israel after the death of Ahab.
[1:2] And Ahaziah fell down through a lattice in his upper chamber that was in Samaria, and was sick: and he sent messengers, and said unto them, Go, enquire of Baalzebub the god of Ekron whether I shall recover of this disease.
[1:3] But the angel of the LORD said to Elijah the Tishbite, Arise, go up to meet the messengers of the king of Samaria, and say unto them, Is it not because there is not a God in Israel, that ye go to enquire of Baalzebub the god of Ekron?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/12-2-kings-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/12-2-kings-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>2 Kings - World English Bible (WEB) [1:1] Moab rebelled against Israel after the death of Ahab.
[1:2] Ahaziah fell down through the lattice in his upper chamber that was in Samaria, and was sick: and he sent messengers, and said to them, Go, inquire of Baal Zebub, the god of Ekron, whether I shall recover of this sickness.
[1:3] But the angel of Yahweh said to Elijah the Tishbite, Arise, go up to meet the messengers of the king of Samaria, and tell them, Is it because there is no God in Israel, that you go to inquire of Baal Zebub, the god of Ekron?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/12-2-kings-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/12-2-kings-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>2 Kings - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And Moab transgresseth against Israel after the death of Ahab,
[1:2] and Ahaziah falleth through the lattice in his upper chamber that is&#39; in Samaria, and is sick, and sendeth messengers, and saith unto them, Go ye, inquire of Baal-Zebub god of Ekron if I recover from this sickness.&amp;rsquo;
[1:3] And a messenger of Jehovah hath spoken unto Elijah the Tishbite, `Rise, go up to meet the messengers of the king of Samaria, and speak unto them, Is it because there is not a God in Israel &amp;ndash; ye are going to inquire of Baal Zebub god of Ekron?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>