<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Micah on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/micah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Micah on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/micah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/33-micah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/33-micah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>Micah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV) [1:1] The word of Jehovah that came to Micah the Morashtite in the days of Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, which he saw concerning Samaria and Jerusalem.
[1:2] Hear, ye peoples, all of you: hearken, O earth, and all that therein is: and let the Lord Jehovah be witness against you, the Lord from his holy temple.
[1:3] For, behold, Jehovah cometh forth out of his place, and will come down, and tread upon the high places of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/33-micah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/33-micah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Micah - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The word of the Lord which came to Micah the Morashtite, in the days of Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah: his vision about Samaria and Jerusalem.
[1:2] Give ear, you peoples, all of you; give attention, O earth and everything in it: let the Lord God be witness against you, the Lord from his holy Temple.
[1:3] For see, the Lord is coming out from his place, and will come down, stepping on the high places of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/33-micah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/33-micah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>Micah - King James Version (KJV) [1:1] The word of the LORD that came to Micah the Morasthite in the days of Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, which he saw concerning Samaria and Jerusalem.
[1:2] Hear, all ye people; hearken, O earth, and all that therein is: and let the Lord GOD be witness against you, the LORD from his holy temple.
[1:3] For, behold, the LORD cometh forth out of his place, and will come down, and tread upon the high places of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/33-micah-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/33-micah-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>Micah - World English Bible (WEB) [1:1] The word of Yahweh that came to Micah the Morashtite in the days of Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, which he saw concerning Samaria and Jerusalem.
[1:2] Hear, you peoples, all of you. Listen, O earth, and all that is therein: And let the Lord Yahweh be witness against you, The Lord from his holy temple.
[1:3] For, behold, Yahweh comes forth out of his place, And will come down and tread on the high places of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/33-micah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/33-micah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Micah - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A word of Jehovah that hath been unto Micah the Morashite in the days of Jotham, Ahaz, Hezekiah, kings of Judah, that he hath seen concerning Samaria and Jerusalem:
[1:2] Hear, O peoples, all of them! Attend, O earth, and its fulness, And the Lord Jehovah is against you for a witness, The Lord from His holy temple.
[1:3] For lo, Jehovah is going out from His place, And He hath come down, And hath trodden on high places of earth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>