<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Habakkuk on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/habakkuk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Habakkuk on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/habakkuk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Habakkuk - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/35-habakkuk-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/35-habakkuk-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden which Habakkuk the prophet did see.
[1:2] O Jehovah, how long shall I cry, and thou wilt not hear? I cry out unto thee of violence, and thou wilt not save.
[1:3] Why dost thou show me iniquity, and look upon perverseness? for destruction and violence are before me; and there is strife, and contention riseth up.
[1:4] Therefore the law is slacked, and justice doth never go forth; for the wicked doth compass about the righteous; therefore justice goeth forth perverted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habakkuk - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/35-habakkuk-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/35-habakkuk-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word which Habakkuk the prophet saw.
[1:2] How long, O Lord, will your ears be shut to my voice? I make an outcry to you about violent behaviour, but you do not send salvation.
[1:3] Why do you make me see evil-doing, and why are my eyes fixed on wrong? for wasting and violent acts are before me: and there is fighting and bitter argument.
[1:4] For this reason the law is feeble and decisions are not effected: for the upright man is circled round by evil-doers; because of which right is twisted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habakkuk - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/35-habakkuk-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/35-habakkuk-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden which Habakkuk the prophet did see.
[1:2] O LORD, how long shall I cry, and thou wilt not hear! even cry out unto thee of violence, and thou wilt not save!
[1:3] Why dost thou shew me iniquity, and cause me to behold grievance? for spoiling and violence are before me: and there are that raise up strife and contention.
[1:4] Therefore the law is slacked, and judgment doth never go forth: for the wicked doth compass about the righteous; therefore wrong judgment proceedeth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habakkuk - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/35-habakkuk-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/35-habakkuk-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The oracle which Habakkuk the prophet saw.
[1:2] Yahweh, how long will I cry, and you will not hear? I cry out to you &amp;ldquo;Violence!&amp;rdquo; and will you not save?
[1:3] Why do you show me iniquity, and look at perversity? For destruction and violence are before me. There is strife, and contention rises up.
[1:4] Therefore the law is paralyzed, and justice never goes forth; for the wicked surround the righteous; therefore justice goes forth perverted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habakkuk - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/35-habakkuk-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/35-habakkuk-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden that Habakkuk the prophet hath seen:
[1:2] Till when, O Jehovah, have I cried, And Thou dost not hear? I cry unto Thee &amp;ndash; `Violence,&amp;rsquo; and Thou dost not save.
[1:3] Why dost Thou shew me iniquity, And perversity dost cause to behold? And spoiling and violence are&#39; before me, And there is strife, and contention doth lift itself&amp;rsquo; up,
[1:4] Therefore doth law cease, And judgment doth not go forth for ever, For the wicked is compassing the righteous, Therefore wrong judgment goeth forth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>