<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 Samuel on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/2-samuel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 Samuel on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/2-samuel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Samuel - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/10-2-samuel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/10-2-samuel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And it came to pass after the death of Saul, when David was returned from the slaughter of the Amalekites, and David had abode two days in Ziklag;
[1:2] it came to pass on the third day, that, behold, a man came out of the camp from Saul, with his clothes rent, and earth upon his head: and so it was, when he came to David, that he fell to the earth, and did obeisance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Samuel - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/10-2-samuel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/10-2-samuel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now after the death of Saul, when David, having come back from the destruction of the Amalekites, had been in Ziklag for two days;
[1:2] On the third day a man came from Saul&amp;rsquo;s tents, with his clothing out of order and earth on his head: and when he came to David, he went down on the earth and gave him honour.
[1:3] And David said to him, Where have you come from?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Samuel - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/10-2-samuel-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/10-2-samuel-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came to pass after the death of Saul, when David was returned from the slaughter of the Amalekites, and David had abode two days in Ziklag;
[1:2] It came even to pass on the third day, that, behold, a man came out of the camp from Saul with his clothes rent, and earth upon his head: and so it was, when he came to David, that he fell to the earth, and did obeisance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Samuel - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/10-2-samuel-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/10-2-samuel-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] It happened after the death of Saul, when David was returned from the slaughter of the Amalekites, and David had abode two days in Ziklag;
[1:2] it happened on the third day, that behold, a man came out of the camp from Saul, with his clothes torn, and earth on his head: and so it was, when he came to David, that he fell to the earth, and did obeisance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Samuel - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/10-2-samuel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/10-2-samuel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And it cometh to pass, after the death of Saul, that David hath returned from smiting the Amalekite, and David dwelleth in Ziklag two days,
[1:2] and it cometh to pass, on the third day, that lo, a man hath come in out of the camp from Saul, and his garments `are&amp;rsquo; rent, and earth on his head; and it cometh to pass, in his coming in unto David, that he falleth to the earth, and doth obeisance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>