<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>extra-Biblical on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/extra-biblical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in extra-Biblical on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/extra-biblical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>**[1:1]** All wisdom cometh from the Lord, and is with him for ever.</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-all-wisdom-cometh-from-the-lord-and-is-with-him-for-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-all-wisdom-cometh-from-the-lord-and-is-with-him-for-ever/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] All wisdom cometh from the Lord, and is with him for ever.
[1:2] Who can number the sand of the sea, and the drops of rain, and the days of eternity?
[1:3] Who can find out the height of heaven, and the breadth of the earth, and the deep, and wisdom?
[1:4] Wisdom hath been created before all things, and the understanding of prudence from everlasting.
[1:5] The word of God most high is the fountain of wisdom; and her ways are everlasting commandments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**[1:1]** And these are the words of the book, which Baruch the son of Nerias, the son of Maasias, the son of Sedecias, the son of Asadias, the son of Chelcias, wrote in Babylon,</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-and-these-are-the-words-of-the-book-which-baruch-the-son-of-nerias-the-son-of-maasias-the-son-of-sedecias-the-son-of-asadias-the-son-of-chelcias-wrote-in-babylon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-and-these-are-the-words-of-the-book-which-baruch-the-son-of-nerias-the-son-of-maasias-the-son-of-sedecias-the-son-of-asadias-the-son-of-chelcias-wrote-in-babylon/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And these are the words of the book, which Baruch the son of Nerias, the son of Maasias, the son of Sedecias, the son of Asadias, the son of Chelcias, wrote in Babylon,
[1:2] In the fifth year, and in the seventh day of the month, what time as the Chaldeans took Jerusalem, and burnt it with fire.
[1:3] And Baruch did read the words of this book in the hearing of Jechonias the son of Joachim king of Juda, and in the ears of all the people that came to hear the book,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**[1:1]** In the twelfth year of the reign of Nabuchodonosor, who reigned in Nineve, the great city; in the days of Arphaxad, which reigned over the Medes in Ecbatane,</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-in-the-twelfth-year-of-the-reign-of-nabuchodonosor-who-reigned-in-nineve-the-great-city-in-the-days-of-arphaxad-which-reigned-over-the-medes-in-ecbatane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-in-the-twelfth-year-of-the-reign-of-nabuchodonosor-who-reigned-in-nineve-the-great-city-in-the-days-of-arphaxad-which-reigned-over-the-medes-in-ecbatane/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the twelfth year of the reign of Nabuchodonosor, who reigned in Nineve, the great city; in the days of Arphaxad, which reigned over the Medes in Ecbatane,
[1:2] And built in Ecbatane walls round about of stones hewn three cubits broad and six cubits long, and made the height of the wall seventy cubits, and the breadth thereof fifty cubits:
[1:3] And set the towers thereof upon the gates of it an hundred cubits high, and the breadth thereof in the foundation threescore cubits:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**[1:1]** Love righteousness, ye that be judges of the earth: think of the Lord with a good (heart,) and in simplicity of heart seek him.</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-love-righteousness-ye-that-be-judges-of-the-earth-think-of-the-lord-with-a-good-heart-and-in-simplicity-of-heart-seek-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-love-righteousness-ye-that-be-judges-of-the-earth-think-of-the-lord-with-a-good-heart-and-in-simplicity-of-heart-seek-him/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Love righteousness, ye that be judges of the earth: think of the Lord with a good (heart,) and in simplicity of heart seek him.
[1:2] For he will be found of them that tempt him not; and sheweth himself unto such as do not distrust him.
[1:3] For froward thoughts separate from God: and his power, when it is tried, reproveth the unwise.
[1:4] For into a malicious soul wisdom shall not enter; nor dwell in the body that is subject unto sin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**[1:1]** The book of the words of Tobit, son of Tobiel, the son of Ananiel, the son of Aduel, the son of Gabael, of the seed of Asael, of the tribe of Nephthali;</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-the-book-of-the-words-of-tobit-son-of-tobiel-the-son-of-ananiel-the-son-of-aduel-the-son-of-gabael-of-the-seed-of-asael-of-the-tribe-of-nephthali/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-the-book-of-the-words-of-tobit-son-of-tobiel-the-son-of-ananiel-the-son-of-aduel-the-son-of-gabael-of-the-seed-of-asael-of-the-tribe-of-nephthali/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The book of the words of Tobit, son of Tobiel, the son of Ananiel, the son of Aduel, the son of Gabael, of the seed of Asael, of the tribe of Nephthali;
[1:2] Who in the time of Enemessar king of the Assyrians was led captive out of Thisbe, which is at the right hand of that city, which is called properly Nephthali in Galilee above Aser.
[1:3] I Tobit have walked all the days of my life in the ways of truth and justice, and I did many almsdeeds to my brethren, and my nation, who came with me to Nineve, into the land of the Assyrians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**[1:1]** The brethren, the Jews that be at Jerusalem and in the land of Judea, wish unto the brethren, the Jews that are throughout Egypt health and peace:</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-the-brethren-the-jews-that-be-at-jerusalem-and-in-the-land-of-judea-wish-unto-the-brethren-the-jews-that-are-throughout-egypt-health-and-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-the-brethren-the-jews-that-be-at-jerusalem-and-in-the-land-of-judea-wish-unto-the-brethren-the-jews-that-are-throughout-egypt-health-and-peace/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The brethren, the Jews that be at Jerusalem and in the land of Judea, wish unto the brethren, the Jews that are throughout Egypt health and peace:
[1:2] God be gracious unto you, and remember his covenant that he made with Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob, his faithful servants;
[1:3] And give you all an heart to serve him, and to do his will, with a good courage and a willing mind;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**[1:1]** The Second Coming of Christ and Resurrection of the Dead (which Christ revealed unto Peter) who died because of their sins, for that they kept not the commandment of God their creator.</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-the-second-coming-of-christ-and-resurrection-of-the-dead-which-christ-revealed-unto-peter-who-died-because-of-their-sins-for-that-they-kept-not-the-commandment-of-god-their-creator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-1-the-second-coming-of-christ-and-resurrection-of-the-dead-which-christ-revealed-unto-peter-who-died-because-of-their-sins-for-that-they-kept-not-the-commandment-of-god-their-creator/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Second Coming of Christ and Resurrection of the Dead (which Christ revealed unto Peter) who died because of their sins, for that they kept not the commandment of God their creator.
[1:2] And he (Peter) pondered thereon, that he might perceive the mystery of the Son of God, the merciful and lover of mercy.
[1:3] And when the Lord was seated upon the Mount of Olives, his disciples came unto him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Adam and Eve</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-adam-and-eve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-adam-and-eve/</guid>
      <description>1 Adam and Eve [1:1] On the third day, God planted the garden in the east of the earth, on the border of the world eastward, beyond which, towards the sun-rising, one finds nothing but water, that encompasses the whole world, and reaches to the borders of heaven.
[1:2] And to the north of the garden there is a sea of water, clear and pure to the taste, unlike anything else; so that, through the clearness thereof, one may look into the depths of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Enoch</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-enoch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-enoch/</guid>
      <description>1 Enoch [1:1] The words of the blessing of Enoch, wherewith he blessed the elect ⌈⌈and⌉⌉ righteous, who will be living in the day of tribulation, when all the wicked ⌈⌈and godless⌉⌉ are to be removed. [1:2] And he took up his parable and said&amp;ndash;Enoch a righteous man, whose eyes were opened by God, saw the vision of the Holy One in the heavens, ⌈which⌉ the angels showed me, and from them I heard everything, and from them I understood as I saw, but not for this generation, but for a remote one which is for to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Esdras</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-esdras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-esdras/</guid>
      <description>1 Esdras [1:1] And Josias held the feast of the passover in Jerusalem unto his Lord, and offered the passover the fourteenth day of the first month;
[1:2] Having set the priests according to their daily courses, being arrayed in long garments, in the temple of the Lord.
[1:3] And he spake unto the Levites, the holy ministers of Israel, that they should hallow themselves unto the Lord, to set the holy ark of the Lord in the house that king Solomon the son of David had built:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Hermas</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-hermas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-hermas/</guid>
      <description>1 Hermas [1:1] He who had bred me up sold a certain young maid at Rome; whom when I saw many years after, I remembered her, and began to love her as a sister. It happened some time afterwards, that I saw her washing in the river. Tyber; and I reached out my hand unto her, and brought her out of the river,
[1:2] And when I saw her I thought with myself, saying, How happy should I be if I had such a wife, both for beauty and manners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Maccabees</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-maccabees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/1-maccabees/</guid>
      <description>1 Maccabees [1:1] And it happened, after that Alexander son of Philip, the Macedonian, who came out of the land of Chettiim, had smitten Darius king of the Persians and Medes, that he reigned in his stead, the first over Greece,
[1:2] And made many wars, and won many strong holds, and slew the kings of the earth,
[1:3] And went through to the ends of the earth, and took spoils of many nations, insomuch that the earth was quiet before him; whereupon he was exalted and his heart was lifted up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Adam and Eve</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/2-adam-and-eve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/2-adam-and-eve/</guid>
      <description>2 Adam and Eve [1:1] When Luluwa heard Cain&amp;rsquo;s words, she wept and went to call her father and mother, and told them how that Cain had killed his brother Abel.
[1:2] Then they all cried aloud and lifted up their voices, and slapped their faces, and threw dust upon their heads, and rent asunder their garments, and went out and came to the place where Abel was killed.
[1:3] And they found him lying on the earth, killed, and beasts around him; while they wept and cried because of this just one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Enoch</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/2-enoch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/2-enoch/</guid>
      <description>2 Enoch [1:1] There was a wise man, a great artificer, and the Lord conceived love for him and received him, that he should behold the uppermost dwellings and be an eye-witness of the wise and great and inconceivable and immutable realm of God Almighty, of the very wonderful and glorious and bright and many-eyed station of the Lord’s servants, and of the inaccessible throne of the Lord, and of the degrees and manifestations of the incorporeal hosts, and of the ineffable ministration of the multitude of the elements, and of the various apparition and inexpressible singing of the host of Cherubim, and of the boundless light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Esdras</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/2-esdras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/2-esdras/</guid>
      <description>2 Esdras [1:1] The second book of the prophet Esdras, the son of Saraias, the son of Azarias, the son of Helchias, the son of Sadamias, the sou of Sadoc, the son of Achitob,
[1:2] The son of Achias, the son of Phinees, the son of Heli, the son of Amarias, the son of Aziei, the son of Marimoth, the son of And he spake unto the of Borith, the son of Abisei, the son of Phinees, the son of Eleazar,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Hermas</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/2-hermas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/2-hermas/</guid>
      <description>2 Hermas [0:1] When I had prayed at home, and was sat down upon the bed, a certain man came in to me with a reverend look, in the habit of a Shepherd, clothed with a white cloak, having his bag upon his back, and his staff in his hand, and saluted me.
[0:2] I returned his salutation, and immediately he sat down by me, and said unto me, I am sent by that venerable messenger, that I should dwell with thee all the remaining days of thy life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Maccabees</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/2-maccabees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/2-maccabees/</guid>
      <description>2 Maccabees [1:1] The brethren, the Jews that be at Jerusalem and in the land of Judea, wish unto the brethren, the Jews that are throughout Egypt health and peace:
[1:2] God be gracious unto you, and remember his covenant that he made with Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob, his faithful servants;
[1:3] And give you all an heart to serve him, and to do his will, with a good courage and a willing mind;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Enoch</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/3-enoch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/3-enoch/</guid>
      <description>3 Enoch [1:1] When I ascended on high to behold the vision of the Merkaba and had entered the six Halls, one within the other:
[1:2] as soon as I reached the door of the seventh Hall I stood still in prayer before the Holy One, blessed be He, and, lifting up my eyes on high (i.e. towards the Divine Majesty), I said:
[1:3] &amp;ldquo;Lord of the Universe, I pray thee, that the merit of Aaron, the son of Amram, the lover of peace and pursuer of peace, who received the crown of priesthood from Thy Glory on the mount of Sinai, be valid for me in this hour, so that Qafsiel*, the prince, and the angels with him may not get power over me nor throw me down from the heavens &amp;ldquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Hermas</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/3-hermas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/3-hermas/</guid>
      <description>3 Hermas [1:1] And he said onto me; Ye know that ye who are the servants of the Lord, live here as in a pilgrimage; for your city is far off from this city.
[1:2] If, therefore, ye know your city in which ye are to dwell, why do ye here buy estates, and provide yourselves with delicacies, and stately buildings, and supurfluous houses? For he that provides himself these things in this city, does not think of returning into his own city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Additions to Esther 10</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/additions-to-esther-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/additions-to-esther-10/</guid>
      <description>Additions to Esther 10 [10:4] Then Mardocheus said, God hath done these things.
[10:5] For I remember a dream which I saw concerning these matters, and nothing thereof hath failed.
[10:6] A little fountain became a river, and there was light, and the sun, and much water: this river is Esther, whom the king married, and made queen:
[10:7] And the two dragons are I and Aman.
[10:8] And the nations were those that were assembled to destroy the name of the Jews:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apocalypse of Peter</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/apocalypse-of-peter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/apocalypse-of-peter/</guid>
      <description>Apocalypse of Peter [1:1] The Second Coming of Christ and Resurrection of the Dead (which Christ revealed unto Peter) who died because of their sins, for that they kept not the commandment of God their creator.
[1:2] And he (Peter) pondered thereon, that he might perceive the mystery of the Son of God, the merciful and lover of mercy.
[1:3] And when the Lord was seated upon the Mount of Olives, his disciples came unto him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baruch</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/baruch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/baruch/</guid>
      <description>Baruch [1:1] And these are the words of the book, which Baruch the son of Nerias, the son of Maasias, the son of Sedecias, the son of Asadias, the son of Chelcias, wrote in Babylon,
[1:2] In the fifth year, and in the seventh day of the month, what time as the Chaldeans took Jerusalem, and burnt it with fire.
[1:3] And Baruch did read the words of this book in the hearing of Jechonias the son of Joachim king of Juda, and in the ears of all the people that came to hear the book,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bel and the Dragon</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/bel-and-the-dragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/bel-and-the-dragon/</guid>
      <description>Bel and the Dragon [1:1] And king Astyages was gathered to his fathers, and Cyrus of Persia received his kingdom.
[1:2] And Daniel conversed with the king, and was honoured above all his friends.
[1:3] Now the Babylons had an idol, called Bel, and there were spent upon him every day twelve great measures of fine flour, and forty sheep, and six vessels of wine.
[1:4] And the king worshipped it and went daily to adore it: but Daniel worshipped his own God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fourth Baruch</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/fourth-baruch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/fourth-baruch/</guid>
      <description>Fourth Baruch [1:1] It came to pass, when the children of Israel were taken captive by the king of the Chaldeans, that God spoke to Jeremiah saying: Jeremiah, my chosen one, arise and depart from this city, you and Baruch, since I am going to destroy it because of the multitude of the sins of those who dwell in it.
[1:2] For your prayers are like a solid pillar in its midst, and like an indestructible wall surrounding it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasher</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/jasher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/jasher/</guid>
      <description>Jasher [1:1] And God said, Let us make man in our image, after our likeness, and God created man in his own image.
[1:2] And God formed man from the ground, and he blew into his nostrils the breath of life, and man became a living soul endowed with speech.
[1:3] And the Lord said, It is not good for man to be alone; I will make unto him a helpmeet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jubilees</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/jubilees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/jubilees/</guid>
      <description>Jubilees [1:1] And it came to pass in the first year of the exodus of the children of Israel out of Egypt, in the third month, on the sixteenth day of the month, [2450 Anno Mundi] that God spake to Moses, saying: &amp;lsquo;Come up to Me on the Mount, and I will give thee two tables of stone of the law and of the commandment, which I have written, that thou mayst teach them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judith</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/judith/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/judith/</guid>
      <description>Judith [1:1] In the twelfth year of the reign of Nabuchodonosor, who reigned in Nineve, the great city; in the days of Arphaxad, which reigned over the Medes in Ecbatane,
[1:2] And built in Ecbatane walls round about of stones hewn three cubits broad and six cubits long, and made the height of the wall seventy cubits, and the breadth thereof fifty cubits:
[1:3] And set the towers thereof upon the gates of it an hundred cubits high, and the breadth thereof in the foundation threescore cubits:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer of Azariah</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/prayer-of-azariah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/prayer-of-azariah/</guid>
      <description>Prayer of Azariah [1:1] And they walked in the midst of the fire, praising God, and blessing the Lord.
[1:2] Then Azarias stood up, and prayed on this manner; and opening his mouth in the midst of the fire said,
[1:3] Blessed art thou, O Lord God of our fathers: thy name is worthy to be praised and glorified for evermore:
[1:4] For thou art righteous in all the things that thou hast done to us: yea, true are all thy works, thy ways are right, and all thy judgments truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer of Manasseh</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/prayer-of-manasseh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/prayer-of-manasseh/</guid>
      <description>Prayer of Manasseh [1:1] O Lord, Almighty God of our fathers, Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob, and of their righteous seed;
[1:2] who hast made heaven and earth, with all the ornament thereof;
[1:3] who hast bound the sea by the word of thy commandment; who hast shut up the deep, and sealed it by thy terrible and glorious name;
[1:4] whom all men fear, and tremble before thy power; for the majesty of thy glory cannot be borne, and thine angry threatening toward sinners is importable:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Baruch</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/second-baruch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/second-baruch/</guid>
      <description>Second Baruch [1:1] And it came to pass in the twenty-fifth year of Jeconiah, king of Judah, that the word of the Lord came to Baruch, the son of Neriah,
[1:2] and said to him: &amp;lsquo;Hast thou seen all that this people are doing to Me, that the evils which these two tribes which remained have done are greater than (those of) the ten tribes which were carried away captive?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sirach</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/sirach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/sirach/</guid>
      <description>Sirach [1:1] All wisdom cometh from the Lord, and is with him for ever.
[1:2] Who can number the sand of the sea, and the drops of rain, and the days of eternity?
[1:3] Who can find out the height of heaven, and the breadth of the earth, and the deep, and wisdom?
[1:4] Wisdom hath been created before all things, and the understanding of prudence from everlasting.
[1:5] The word of God most high is the fountain of wisdom; and her ways are everlasting commandments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Susanna</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/susanna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/susanna/</guid>
      <description>Susanna [1:1] There dwelt a man in Babylon, called Joacim:
[1:2] And he took a wife, whose name was Susanna, the daughter of Chelcias, a very fair woman, and one that feared the Lord.
[1:3] Her parents also were righteous, and taught their daughter according to the law of Moses.
[1:4] Now Joacim was a great rich man, and had a fair garden joining unto his house: and to him resorted the Jews; because he was more honourable than all others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testament of Solomon</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testament-of-solomon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testament-of-solomon/</guid>
      <description>Testament of Solomon [1:1] Testament of Solomon, son of David, who was king in Jerusalem, and mastered and controlled all spirits of the air, on the earth, and under the earth. By means of them also he wrought all the transcendent works of the Temple. Telling also of the authorities they wield against men, and by what angels these demons are brought to naught. Of the sage Solomon. Blessed art thou, O Lord God, who didst give Solomon such authority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Asher</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-asher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-asher/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Asher [1:1] THE copy of the Testament To Asher, what things he spake to his sons in the hundred and twenty-fifth year of his life.
[1:2] For while he was still in health, he said to them: Hearken, ye children of Asher, to your father, and I will declare to you all that is upright in the sight of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Benjamin</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-benjamin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-benjamin/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Benjamin [1:1] THE copy of the words of Benjamin, which he commanded his sons to observe, after he had lived a hundred and twenty-five years.
[1:2] And he kissed them, and said: As Isaac was born to Abraham in his old age, so also was I to Jacob.
[1:3] And since Rachel my mother died in giving me birth, I had no milk; therefore I was suckled by Bilhah her handmaid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Dan</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-dan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-dan/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Dan [1:1] THE copy of the words of Dan, which he spake to his sons in his last days, in the hundred and twenty-fifth year of his life.
[1:2] For he called together his I family, and said: Hearken to my words, ye sons of Dan; and give heed to the words of your father.
[1:3] I have proved in my heart, and in my whole life, that truth with just dealing is good and well pleasing to God, and that lying and anger are evil, because they teach man all wickedness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Gad</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-gad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-gad/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Gad [1:1] THE copy of the testament of Gad, what things he spake unto his sons, in the hundred and twenty-fifth year of his life, saying unto them:
[1:2] Hearken, my children, I was the ninth son born to Jacob, and I was valiant in keeping the flocks.
[1:3] Accordingly I guarded at night the flock; and whenever the lion came, or the wolf, or any wild beast against the fold, I pursued it, and overtaking it I seized its foot with my hand and hurled it about a stone&amp;rsquo;s throw, and so killed it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Issachar</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-issachar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-issachar/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Issachar [1:1] THE copy of the words of Issachar.
[1:2] For he called his sons and said to them: Hearken, my children, to Issachar your father; give ear to the words of him who is beloved of the Lord.
[1:3] I was born the fifth son to Jacob, by way of hire for the mandrakes.
[1:4] For Reuben my brother brought in mandrakes from the field, and Rachel met him and took them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Joseph</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-joseph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-joseph/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Joseph [1:1] THE copy of the Testament of Joseph.
[1:2] When he was about to die he called his sons and his brethren together, and said to them:&amp;ndash;
[1:3] My brethren and my children, hearken to Joseph the beloved of Israel; give ear, my sons, unto your father.
[1:4] I have seen in my life envy and death, yet I went not astray, but persevered in the truth&amp;ndash;of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Judah</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-judah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-judah/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Judah [1:1] THE copy of the words of Judah, what things he spake to his sons before he died.
[1:2] They gathered themselves together, therefore, and came to him, and he said to them: Hearken, my children, to Judah your father.
[1:3] I was the fourth son born to my father Jacob; and Leah my mother named me Judah, saying, I give thanks to the Lord, because He hath given me a fourth son also.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Levi</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-levi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-levi/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Levi [1:1] THE copy of the words of Levi, the things which he ordained unto his sons, according to all that they should do, and what things should befall them until the day of judgement.
[1:2] He was sound in health when he called them to him; for it had been revealed to him that he should die.
[1:3] And when they were gathered together he said to them:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Naphtali</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-naphtali/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-naphtali/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Naphtali [1:1] THE copy of, the testament of Naphtali, which he ordained at the time of his death in the hundred and thirtieth year of his life.
[1:2] When his sons were gathered together in the seventh month, on the first day of the month, while still in good health, he made them a feast of food and wine.
[1:3] And after he was awake in the morning, he said to them, I am dying; and they believed him not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Reuben</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-reuben/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-reuben/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Reuben [1:1] THE Copy of the Testament of Reuben, even the commands which he gave his sons before he died in the hundred and twenty-fifth year of his life.
[1:2] Two years after the death of Joseph his brother, when Reuben fell ill, his sons and his sons&amp;rsquo; sons were gathered together to visit him.
[1:3] And he said to them: My children, behold I am dying, and go the way of my fathers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Simeon</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-simeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-simeon/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Simeon [1:1] THE copy of the words of Simeon, the things which he spake to his sons before he died, in the hundred and twentieth year of his life, at which time Joseph, his brother, died.
[1:2] For when Simeon was sick, his sons came to visit him. and he strengthened himself and sat up and kissed them, and said:&amp;ndash;
[1:3] Hearken, my children, to Simeon your father and I will declare unto you what things I have in my heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Zebulun</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-zebulun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/testaments-of-the-twelve-patriarchs-the-testament-of-zebulun/</guid>
      <description>Testaments of the Twelve Patriarchs / The Testament of Zebulun [1:1] THE copy of the words of Zebulun, which he enjoined on his sons before he died in the hundred and fourteenth year of his life, two years after the death of Joseph.
[1:2] And he said to them: Hearken to me, ye sons of Zebulun attend to the words of your father.
[1:3] I, Zebulun, was born a good gift to my parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Apocalipse of Sedrach</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/the-apocalipse-of-sedrach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/the-apocalipse-of-sedrach/</guid>
      <description>The Apocalipse of Sedrach [1:1] Beloved, let us prefer nothing in honor except sincere love: for in many things we stumble every day and night and hour. And for this cause let us gain love, for it covereth a multitude of sins: for what is the profit, my children, if we have all things, and have not saving love… O blessed love, supplier of all good things. Blessed is the man who has gained the true faith and sincere love, according as the Master said, there is no greater love than this that a man should lay down his life for his friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ascension of Isaiah</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/the-ascension-of-isaiah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/the-ascension-of-isaiah/</guid>
      <description>The Ascension of Isaiah [1:1] And it came to pass in the twenty-sixth year of the reign of Hezediah king of Judah that he called Manasseh his son. Now he was his only one.
[1:2] And he called him into the presence of Isaiah the son of Amoz the prophet, and into the presence of Josab the son of Isaiah, in order to deliver unto him the words of righteousness which the king himself had seen:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third Baruch</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/third-baruch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/third-baruch/</guid>
      <description>Third Baruch [0:0] A narrative and revelation of Baruch, concerning those ineffable things which he saw by command of God. Bless Thou, O Lord.
[0:0] A revelation of Baruch, who stood upon the river Gel weeping over the captivity of Jerusalem, when also Abimelech was preserved by the hand of God, at the farm of Agrippa. And he was sitting thus at the beautiful gates, where the Holy of holies lay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tobit</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/tobit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/tobit/</guid>
      <description>Tobit [1:1] The book of the words of Tobit, son of Tobiel, the son of Ananiel, the son of Aduel, the son of Gabael, of the seed of Asael, of the tribe of Nephthali;
[1:2] Who in the time of Enemessar king of the Assyrians was led captive out of Thisbe, which is at the right hand of that city, which is called properly Nephthali in Galilee above Aser.
[1:3] I Tobit have walked all the days of my life in the ways of truth and justice, and I did many almsdeeds to my brethren, and my nation, who came with me to Nineve, into the land of the Assyrians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wisdom</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/wisdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/extrabiblical/wisdom/</guid>
      <description>Wisdom [1:1] Love righteousness, ye that be judges of the earth: think of the Lord with a good (heart,) and in simplicity of heart seek him.
[1:2] For he will be found of them that tempt him not; and sheweth himself unto such as do not distrust him.
[1:3] For froward thoughts separate from God: and his power, when it is tried, reproveth the unwise.
[1:4] For into a malicious soul wisdom shall not enter; nor dwell in the body that is subject unto sin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>