<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 Timothy on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/2-timothy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 Timothy on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/2-timothy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Timothy - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/55-2-timothy-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/55-2-timothy-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Christ Jesus through the will of God, according to the promise of the life which is in Christ Jesus,
[1:2] to Timothy, my beloved child: Grace, mercy, peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] I thank God, whom I serve from my forefathers in a pure conscience, how unceasing is my remembrance of thee in my supplications, night and day
[1:4] longing to see thee, remembering thy tears, that I may be filled with joy;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Timothy - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/55-2-timothy-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/55-2-timothy-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an Apostle of Jesus Christ by the purpose of God, in the hope of the life which is in Christ Jesus,
[1:2] To Timothy, my well-loved child: Grace, mercy, peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] I give praise to God, whose servant I have been, with a heart free from sin, from the time of my fathers, because in my prayers at all times the thought of you is with me, night and day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Timothy - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/55-2-timothy-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/55-2-timothy-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ by the will of God, according to the promise of life which is in Christ Jesus,
[1:2] To Timothy, my dearly beloved son: Grace, mercy, and peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] I thank God, whom I serve from my forefathers with pure conscience, that without ceasing I have remembrance of thee in my prayers night and day;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Timothy - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/55-2-timothy-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/55-2-timothy-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ through the will of God, according to the promise of the life which is in Christ Jesus,
[1:2] to Timothy, my beloved child: Grace, mercy, and peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] I thank God, whom I serve as my forefathers did, with a pure conscience. How unceasing is my memory of you in my petitions, night and day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Timothy - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/55-2-timothy-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/55-2-timothy-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ, through the will of God, according to a promise of life that `is&amp;rsquo; in Christ Jesus,
[1:2] to Timotheus, beloved child: Grace, kindness, peace, from God the Father, and Christ Jesus our Lord!
[1:3] I am thankful to God, whom I serve from progenitors in a pure conscience, that unceasingly I have remembrance concerning thee in my supplications night and day,
[1:4] desiring greatly to see thee, being mindful of thy tears, that with joy I may be filled,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>