<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Haggai on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/haggai/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Haggai on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/haggai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Haggai - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/37-haggai-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/37-haggai-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the second year of Darius the king, in the sixth month, in the first day of the month, came the word of Jehovah by Haggai the prophet unto Zerubbabel the son of Shealtiel, governor of Judah, and to Joshua the son of Jehozadak, the high priest, saying,
[1:2] Thus speaketh Jehovah of hosts, saying, This people say, It is not the time `for us&amp;rsquo; to come, the time for Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s house to be built.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haggai - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/37-haggai-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/37-haggai-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the second year of Darius the king, in the sixth month, on the first day of the month, came the word of the Lord by Haggai the prophet to Zerubbabel, the son of Shealtiel, ruler of Judah, and to Joshua, the son of Jehozadak, the high priest, saying,
[1:2] These are the words of the Lord of armies: These people say, The time has not come for building the Lord&amp;rsquo;s house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haggai - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/37-haggai-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/37-haggai-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the second year of Darius the king, in the sixth month, in the first day of the month, came the word of the LORD by Haggai the prophet unto Zerubbabel the son of Shealtiel, governor of Judah, and to Joshua the son of Josedech, the high priest, saying,
[1:2] Thus speaketh the LORD of hosts, saying, This people say, The time is not come, the time that the LORD&amp;rsquo;s house should be built.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haggai - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/37-haggai-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/37-haggai-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the second year of Darius the king, in the sixth month, in the first day of the month, the Word of Yahweh came by Haggai, the prophet, to Zerubbabel, the son of Shealtiel, governor of Judah, and to Joshua, the son of Jehozadak, the high priest, saying,
[1:2] &amp;ldquo;This is what Yahweh of Hosts says: These people say, &amp;lsquo;The time hasn&amp;rsquo;t yet come, the time for Yahweh&amp;rsquo;s house to be built.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haggai - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/37-haggai-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/37-haggai-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the second year of Darius the king, in the sixth month, in the first day of the month, hath a word of Jehovah been by the hand of Haggai the prophet, unto Zerubbabel son of Shealtiel, governor of Judah, and unto Joshua son of Josedech, the high priest, saying:
[1:2] Thus spake Jehovah of Hosts, saying: This people! &amp;ndash; they have said, The time hath not come, The time the house of Jehovah is&amp;rsquo; to be built.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>