<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Psalms on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/psalms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Psalms on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/psalms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Psalms - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/19-psalms-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/19-psalms-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Blessed is the man that walketh not in the counsel of the wicked, Nor standeth in the way of sinners, Nor sitteth in the seat of scoffers:
[1:2] But his delight is in the law of Jehovah; And on his law doth he meditate day and night.
[1:3] And he shall be like a tree planted by the streams of water, That bringeth forth its fruit in its season, Whose leaf also doth not wither; And whatsoever he doeth shall prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psalms - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/19-psalms-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/19-psalms-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Happy is the man who does not go in the company of sinners, or take his place in the way of evil-doers, or in the seat of those who do not give honour to the Lord.
[1:2] But whose delight is in the law of the Lord, and whose mind is on his law day and night.
[1:3] He will be like a tree planted by the rivers of water, which gives its fruit at the right time, whose leaves will ever be green; and he will do well in all his undertakings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psalms - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/19-psalms-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/19-psalms-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Blessed is the man that walketh not in the counsel of the ungodly, nor standeth in the way of sinners, nor sitteth in the seat of the scornful.
[1:2] But his delight is in the law of the LORD; and in his law doth he meditate day and night.
[1:3] And he shall be like a tree planted by the rivers of water, that bringeth forth his fruit in his season; his leaf also shall not wither; and whatsoever he doeth shall prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psalms - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/19-psalms-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/19-psalms-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Blessed is the man who doesn&amp;rsquo;t walk in the counsel of the wicked, Nor stand in the way of sinners, Nor sit in the seat of scoffers;
[1:2] But his delight is in Yahweh&amp;rsquo;s law; On his law he meditates day and night.
[1:3] He will be like a tree planted by the streams of water, That brings forth its fruit in its season, Whose leaf also does not wither.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psalms - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/19-psalms-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/19-psalms-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] O the happiness of that one, who Hath not walked in the counsel of the wicked. And in the way of sinners hath not stood, And in the seat of scorners hath not sat;
[1:2] But &amp;ndash; in the law of Jehovah `is&amp;rsquo; his delight, And in His law he doth meditate by day and by night:
[1:3] And he hath been as a tree, Planted by rivulets of water, That giveth its fruit in its season, And its leaf doth not wither, And all that he doth he causeth to prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>