<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 Samuel on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/1-samuel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 Samuel on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/1-samuel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Samuel - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/9-1-samuel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/9-1-samuel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now there was a certain man of Ramathaim-zophim, of the hill-country of Ephraim, and his name was Elkanah, the son of Jeroham, the son of Elihu, the son of Tohu, the son of Zuph, an Ephraimite:
[1:2] and he had two wives; the name of the one was Hannah, and the name of other Peninnah: and Peninnah had children, but Hannah had no children.
[1:3] And this man went up out of his city from year to year to worship and to sacrifice unto Jehovah of hosts in Shiloh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Samuel - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/9-1-samuel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/9-1-samuel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now there was a certain man of Ramathaim, a Zuphite of the hill-country of Ephraim, named Elkanah; he was the son of Jeroham, the son of Elihu, the son of Tohu, the son of Zuph, an Ephraimite:
[1:2] And he had two wives, one named Hannah and the other Peninnah: and Peninnah was the mother of children, but Hannah had no children.
[1:3] Now this man went up from his town every year to give worship and to make offerings to the Lord of armies in Shiloh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Samuel - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/9-1-samuel-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/9-1-samuel-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now there was a certain man of Ramathaimzophim, of mount Ephraim, and his name was Elkanah, the son of Jeroham, the son of Elihu, the son of Tohu, the son of Zuph, an Ephrathite:
[1:2] And he had two wives; the name of the one was Hannah, and the name of the other Peninnah: and Peninnah had children, but Hannah had no children.
[1:3] And this man went up out of his city yearly to worship and to sacrifice unto the LORD of hosts in Shiloh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Samuel - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/9-1-samuel-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/9-1-samuel-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now there was a certain man of Ramathaim Zophim, of the hill-country of Ephraim, and his name was Elkanah, the son of Jeroham, the son of Elihu, the son of Tohu, the son of Zuph, an Ephraimite:
[1:2] and he had two wives; the name of the one was Hannah, and the name of other Peninnah: and Peninnah had children, but Hannah had no children.
[1:3] This man went up out of his city from year to year to worship and to sacrifice to Yahweh of Hosts in Shiloh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Samuel - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/9-1-samuel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/9-1-samuel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And there is a certain man of Ramathaim-Zophim, of the hill-country of Ephraim, and his name `is&amp;rsquo; Elkanah, son of Jeroham, son of Elihu, son of Tohu, son of Zuph, and Ephrathite,
[1:2] and he hath two wives, the name of the one `is&amp;rsquo; Hannah, and the name of the second Peninnah, and Peninnah hath children, and Hannah hath no children.
[1:3] And that man hath gone up out of his city from time to time, to bow himself, and to sacrifice, before Jehovah of Hosts, in Shiloh, and there `are&amp;rsquo; two sons of Eli, Hophni and Phinehas, priests to Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>