<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ezekiel on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/ezekiel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ezekiel on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/ezekiel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/26-ezekiel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/26-ezekiel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came to pass in the thirtieth year, in the fourth month&#39;, in the fifth day&amp;rsquo; of the month, as I was among the captives by the river Chebar, that the heavens were opened, and I saw visions of God.
[1:2] In the fifth `day&amp;rsquo; of the month, which was the fifth year of king Jehoiachin&amp;rsquo;s captivity,
[1:3] the word of Jehovah came expressly unto Ezekiel the priest, the son of Buzi, in the land of the Chaldeans by the river Chebar; and the hand of Jehovah was there upon him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/26-ezekiel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/26-ezekiel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came about in the thirtieth year, in the fourth month, on the fifth day of the month, while I was by the river Chebar among those who had been made prisoners, that the heavens were made open and I saw visions of God.
[1:2] On the fifth day of the month, in the fifth year after King Jehoiachin had been made a prisoner,
[1:3] The word of the Lord came to me, Ezekiel the priest, the son of Buzi, in the land of the Chaldaeans by the river Chebar; and the hand of the Lord was on me there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/26-ezekiel-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/26-ezekiel-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came to pass in the thirtieth year, in the fourth month, in the fifth day of the month, as I was among the captives by the river of Chebar, that the heavens were opened, and I saw visions of God.
[1:2] In the fifth day of the month, which was the fifth year of king Jehoiachin&amp;rsquo;s captivity,
[1:3] The word of the LORD came expressly unto Ezekiel the priest, the son of Buzi, in the land of the Chaldeans by the river Chebar; and the hand of the LORD was there upon him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/26-ezekiel-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/26-ezekiel-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it happened in the thirtieth year, in the fourth [month], in the fifth [day] of the month, as I was among the captives by the river Chebar, that the heavens were opened, and I saw visions of God.
[1:2] In the fifth [day] of the month, which was the fifth year of king Jehoiachin&amp;rsquo;s captivity,
[1:3] the word of Yahweh came expressly to Ezekiel the priest, the son of Buzi, in the land of the Chaldeans by the river Chebar; and the hand of Yahweh was there on him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/26-ezekiel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/26-ezekiel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And it cometh to pass, in the thirtieth year, in the fourth month&#39;, in the fifth of the month, and I am&amp;rsquo; in the midst of the Removed by the river Chebar, the heavens have been opened, and I see visions of God.
[1:2] In the fifth of the month &amp;ndash; it is the fifth year of the removal of the king Jehoiachin &amp;ndash;
[1:3] hath the word of Jehovah certainly been unto Ezekiel son of Buzi the priest, in the land of the Chaldeans, by the river Chebar, and there is on him there a hand of Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>