<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KJV on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/kjv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in KJV on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/kjv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Chronicles - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/13-1-chronicles-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/13-1-chronicles-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Adam, Sheth, Enosh,
[1:2] Kenan, Mahalaleel, Jered,
[1:3] Henoch, Methuselah, Lamech,
[1:4] Noah, Shem, Ham, and Japheth.
[1:5] The sons of Japheth; Gomer, and Magog, and Madai, and Javan, and Tubal, and Meshech, and Tiras.
[1:6] And the sons of Gomer; Ashchenaz, and Riphath, and Togarmah.
[1:7] And the sons of Javan; Elishah, and Tarshish, Kittim, and Dodanim.
[1:8] The sons of Ham; Cush, and Mizraim, Put, and Canaan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/46-1-corinthians-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/46-1-corinthians-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul called to be an apostle of Jesus Christ through the will of God, and Sosthenes our brother,
[1:2] Unto the church of God which is at Corinth, to them that are sanctified in Christ Jesus, called to be saints, with all that in every place call upon the name of Jesus Christ our Lord, both their&amp;rsquo;s and our&amp;rsquo;s:
[1:3] Grace be unto you, and peace, from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 John - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/62-1-john-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/62-1-john-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] That which was from the beginning, which we have heard, which we have seen with our eyes, which we have looked upon, and our hands have handled, of the Word of life;
[1:2] (For the life was manifested, and we have seen it, and bear witness, and shew unto you that eternal life, which was with the Father, and was manifested unto us;)
[1:3] That which we have seen and heard declare we unto you, that ye also may have fellowship with us: and truly our fellowship is with the Father, and with his Son Jesus Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Kings - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/11-1-kings-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/11-1-kings-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now king David was old and stricken in years; and they covered him with clothes, but he gat no heat.
[1:2] Wherefore his servants said unto him, Let there be sought for my lord the king a young virgin: and let her stand before the king, and let her cherish him, and let her lie in thy bosom, that my lord the king may get heat.
[1:3] So they sought for a fair damsel throughout all the coasts of Israel, and found Abishag a Shunammite, and brought her to the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Peter - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/60-1-peter-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/60-1-peter-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Peter, an apostle of Jesus Christ, to the strangers scattered throughout Pontus, Galatia, Cappadocia, Asia, and Bithynia,
[1:2] Elect according to the foreknowledge of God the Father, through sanctification of the Spirit, unto obedience and sprinkling of the blood of Jesus Christ: Grace unto you, and peace, be multiplied.
[1:3] Blessed be the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, which according to his abundant mercy hath begotten us again unto a lively hope by the resurrection of Jesus Christ from the dead,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Samuel - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/9-1-samuel-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/9-1-samuel-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now there was a certain man of Ramathaimzophim, of mount Ephraim, and his name was Elkanah, the son of Jeroham, the son of Elihu, the son of Tohu, the son of Zuph, an Ephrathite:
[1:2] And he had two wives; the name of the one was Hannah, and the name of the other Peninnah: and Peninnah had children, but Hannah had no children.
[1:3] And this man went up out of his city yearly to worship and to sacrifice unto the LORD of hosts in Shiloh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Thessalonians - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/52-1-thessalonians-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/52-1-thessalonians-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, and Silvanus, and Timotheus, unto the church of the Thessalonians which is in God the Father and in the Lord Jesus Christ: Grace be unto you, and peace, from God our Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:2] We give thanks to God always for you all, making mention of you in our prayers;
[1:3] Remembering without ceasing your work of faith, and labour of love, and patience of hope in our Lord Jesus Christ, in the sight of God and our Father;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Timothy - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/54-1-timothy-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/54-1-timothy-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ by the commandment of God our Saviour, and Lord Jesus Christ, which is our hope;
[1:2] Unto Timothy, my own son in the faith: Grace, mercy, and peace, from God our Father and Jesus Christ our Lord.
[1:3] As I besought thee to abide still at Ephesus, when I went into Macedonia, that thou mightest charge some that they teach no other doctrine,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Chronicles - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/14-2-chronicles-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/14-2-chronicles-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And Solomon the son of David was strengthened in his kingdom, and the LORD his God was with him, and magnified him exceedingly.
[1:2] Then Solomon spake unto all Israel, to the captains of thousands and of hundreds, and to the judges, and to every governor in all Israel, the chief of the fathers.
[1:3] So Solomon, and all the congregation with him, went to the high place that was at Gibeon; for there was the tabernacle of the congregation of God, which Moses the servant of the LORD had made in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Corinthians - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/47-2-corinthians-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/47-2-corinthians-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ by the will of God, and Timothy our brother, unto the church of God which is at Corinth, with all the saints which are in all Achaia:
[1:2] Grace be to you and peace from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] Blessed be God, even the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, the Father of mercies, and the God of all comfort;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 John - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/63-2-john-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/63-2-john-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The elder unto the elect lady and her children, whom I love in the truth; and not I only, but also all they that have known the truth;
[1:2] For the truth&amp;rsquo;s sake, which dwelleth in us, and shall be with us for ever.
[1:3] Grace be with you, mercy, and peace, from God the Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ, the Son of the Father, in truth and love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/12-2-kings-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/12-2-kings-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Then Moab rebelled against Israel after the death of Ahab.
[1:2] And Ahaziah fell down through a lattice in his upper chamber that was in Samaria, and was sick: and he sent messengers, and said unto them, Go, enquire of Baalzebub the god of Ekron whether I shall recover of this disease.
[1:3] But the angel of the LORD said to Elijah the Tishbite, Arise, go up to meet the messengers of the king of Samaria, and say unto them, Is it not because there is not a God in Israel, that ye go to enquire of Baalzebub the god of Ekron?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Peter - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/61-2-peter-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/61-2-peter-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Simon Peter, a servant and an apostle of Jesus Christ, to them that have obtained like precious faith with us through the righteousness of God and our Saviour Jesus Christ:
[1:2] Grace and peace be multiplied unto you through the knowledge of God, and of Jesus our Lord,
[1:3] According as his divine power hath given unto us all things that pertain unto life and godliness, through the knowledge of him that hath called us to glory and virtue:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Samuel - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/10-2-samuel-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/10-2-samuel-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came to pass after the death of Saul, when David was returned from the slaughter of the Amalekites, and David had abode two days in Ziklag;
[1:2] It came even to pass on the third day, that, behold, a man came out of the camp from Saul with his clothes rent, and earth upon his head: and so it was, when he came to David, that he fell to the earth, and did obeisance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Thessalonians - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/53-2-thessalonians-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/53-2-thessalonians-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, and Silvanus, and Timotheus, unto the church of the Thessalonians in God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ:
[1:2] Grace unto you, and peace, from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] We are bound to thank God always for you, brethren, as it is meet, because that your faith groweth exceedingly, and the charity of every one of you all toward each other aboundeth;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Timothy - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/55-2-timothy-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/55-2-timothy-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ by the will of God, according to the promise of life which is in Christ Jesus,
[1:2] To Timothy, my dearly beloved son: Grace, mercy, and peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] I thank God, whom I serve from my forefathers with pure conscience, that without ceasing I have remembrance of thee in my prayers night and day;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 John - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/64-3-john-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/64-3-john-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The elder unto the wellbeloved Gaius, whom I love in the truth.
[1:2] Beloved, I wish above all things that thou mayest prosper and be in health, even as thy soul prospereth.
[1:3] For I rejoiced greatly, when the brethren came and testified of the truth that is in thee, even as thou walkest in the truth.
[1:4] I have no greater joy than to hear that my children walk in truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acts - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/44-acts-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/44-acts-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The former treatise have I made, O Theophilus, of all that Jesus began both to do and teach,
[1:2] Until the day in which he was taken up, after that he through the Holy Ghost had given commandments unto the apostles whom he had chosen:
[1:3] To whom also he shewed himself alive after his passion by many infallible proofs, being seen of them forty days, and speaking of the things pertaining to the kingdom of God:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amos - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/30-amos-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/30-amos-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The words of Amos, who was among the herdmen of Tekoa, which he saw concerning Israel in the days of Uzziah king of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam the son of Joash king of Israel, two years before the earthquake.
[1:2] And he said, The LORD will roar from Zion, and utter his voice from Jerusalem; and the habitations of the shepherds shall mourn, and the top of Carmel shall wither.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colossians - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/51-colossians-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/51-colossians-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ by the will of God, and Timotheus our brother,
[1:2] To the saints and faithful brethren in Christ which are at Colosse: Grace be unto you, and peace, from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] We give thanks to God and the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, praying always for you,
[1:4] Since we heard of your faith in Christ Jesus, and of the love which ye have to all the saints,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/27-daniel-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/27-daniel-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the third year of the reign of Jehoiakim king of Judah came Nebuchadnezzar king of Babylon unto Jerusalem, and besieged it.
[1:2] And the Lord gave Jehoiakim king of Judah into his hand, with part of the vessels of the house of God: which he carried into the land of Shinar to the house of his god; and he brought the vessels into the treasure house of his god.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/5-deuteronomy-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/5-deuteronomy-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] These be the words which Moses spake unto all Israel on this side Jordan in the wilderness, in the plain over against the Red sea, between Paran, and Tophel, and Laban, and Hazeroth, and Dizahab.
[1:2] (There are eleven days&amp;rsquo; journey from Horeb by the way of mount Seir unto Kadeshbarnea.)
[1:3] And it came to pass in the fortieth year, in the eleventh month, on the first day of the month, that Moses spake unto the children of Israel, according unto all that the LORD had given him in commandment unto them;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecclesiastes - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/21-ecclesiastes-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/21-ecclesiastes-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The words of the Preacher, the son of David, king in Jerusalem.
[1:2] Vanity of vanities, saith the Preacher, vanity of vanities; all is vanity.
[1:3] What profit hath a man of all his labour which he taketh under the sun?
[1:4] One generation passeth away, and another generation cometh: but the earth abideth for ever.
[1:5] The sun also ariseth, and the sun goeth down, and hasteth to his place where he arose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ephesians - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/49-ephesians-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/49-ephesians-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ by the will of God, to the saints which are at Ephesus, and to the faithful in Christ Jesus:
[1:2] Grace be to you, and peace, from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] Blessed be the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who hath blessed us with all spiritual blessings in heavenly places in Christ:
[1:4] According as he hath chosen us in him before the foundation of the world, that we should be holy and without blame before him in love:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/17-esther-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/17-esther-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came to pass in the days of Ahasuerus, (this is Ahasuerus which reigned, from India even unto Ethiopia, over an hundred and seven and twenty provinces:)
[1:2] That in those days, when the king Ahasuerus sat on the throne of his kingdom, which was in Shushan the palace,
[1:3] In the third year of his reign, he made a feast unto all his princes and his servants; the power of Persia and Media, the nobles and princes of the provinces, being before him:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exodus - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/2-exodus-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/2-exodus-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now these are the names of the children of Israel, which came into Egypt; every man and his household came with Jacob.
[1:2] Reuben, Simeon, Levi, and Judah,
[1:3] Issachar, Zebulun, and Benjamin,
[1:4] Dan, and Naphtali, Gad, and Asher.
[1:5] And all the souls that came out of the loins of Jacob were seventy souls: for Joseph was in Egypt already.
[1:6] And Joseph died, and all his brethren, and all that generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/26-ezekiel-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/26-ezekiel-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came to pass in the thirtieth year, in the fourth month, in the fifth day of the month, as I was among the captives by the river of Chebar, that the heavens were opened, and I saw visions of God.
[1:2] In the fifth day of the month, which was the fifth year of king Jehoiachin&amp;rsquo;s captivity,
[1:3] The word of the LORD came expressly unto Ezekiel the priest, the son of Buzi, in the land of the Chaldeans by the river Chebar; and the hand of the LORD was there upon him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezra - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/15-ezra-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/15-ezra-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now in the first year of Cyrus king of Persia, that the word of the LORD by the mouth of Jeremiah might be fulfilled, the LORD stirred up the spirit of Cyrus king of Persia, that he made a proclamation throughout all his kingdom, and put it also in writing, saying,
[1:2] Thus saith Cyrus king of Persia, The LORD God of heaven hath given me all the kingdoms of the earth; and he hath charged me to build him an house at Jerusalem, which is in Judah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galatians - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/48-galatians-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/48-galatians-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle, (not of men, neither by man, but by Jesus Christ, and God the Father, who raised him from the dead;)
[1:2] And all the brethren which are with me, unto the churches of Galatia:
[1:3] Grace be to you and peace from God the Father, and from our Lord Jesus Christ,
[1:4] Who gave himself for our sins, that he might deliver us from this present evil world, according to the will of God and our Father:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/1-genesis-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/1-genesis-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the beginning God created the heaven and the earth.
[1:2] And the earth was without form, and void; and darkness was upon the face of the deep. And the Spirit of God moved upon the face of the waters.
[1:3] And God said, Let there be light: and there was light.
[1:4] And God saw the light, that it was good: and God divided the light from the darkness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habakkuk - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/35-habakkuk-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/35-habakkuk-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden which Habakkuk the prophet did see.
[1:2] O LORD, how long shall I cry, and thou wilt not hear! even cry out unto thee of violence, and thou wilt not save!
[1:3] Why dost thou shew me iniquity, and cause me to behold grievance? for spoiling and violence are before me: and there are that raise up strife and contention.
[1:4] Therefore the law is slacked, and judgment doth never go forth: for the wicked doth compass about the righteous; therefore wrong judgment proceedeth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haggai - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/37-haggai-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/37-haggai-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the second year of Darius the king, in the sixth month, in the first day of the month, came the word of the LORD by Haggai the prophet unto Zerubbabel the son of Shealtiel, governor of Judah, and to Joshua the son of Josedech, the high priest, saying,
[1:2] Thus speaketh the LORD of hosts, saying, This people say, The time is not come, the time that the LORD&amp;rsquo;s house should be built.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hebrews - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/58-hebrews-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/58-hebrews-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] God, who at sundry times and in divers manners spake in time past unto the fathers by the prophets,
[1:2] Hath in these last days spoken unto us by his Son, whom he hath appointed heir of all things, by whom also he made the worlds;
[1:3] Who being the brightness of his glory, and the express image of his person, and upholding all things by the word of his power, when he had by himself purged our sins, sat down on the right hand of the Majesty on high:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/28-hosea-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/28-hosea-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of the LORD that came unto Hosea, the son of Beeri, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam the son of Joash, king of Israel.
[1:2] The beginning of the word of the LORD by Hosea. And the LORD said to Hosea, Go, take unto thee a wife of whoredoms and children of whoredoms: for the land hath committed great whoredom, departing from the LORD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/23-isaiah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/23-isaiah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The vision of Isaiah the son of Amoz, which he saw concerning Judah and Jerusalem in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah.
[1:2] Hear, O heavens, and give ear, O earth: for the LORD hath spoken, I have nourished and brought up children, and they have rebelled against me.
[1:3] The ox knoweth his owner, and the ass his master&amp;rsquo;s crib: but Israel doth not know, my people doth not consider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/59-james-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/59-james-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] James, a servant of God and of the Lord Jesus Christ, to the twelve tribes which are scattered abroad, greeting.
[1:2] My brethren, count it all joy when ye fall into divers temptations;
[1:3] Knowing this, that the trying of your faith worketh patience.
[1:4] But let patience have her perfect work, that ye may be perfect and entire, wanting nothing.
[1:5] If any of you lack wisdom, let him ask of God, that giveth to all men liberally, and upbraideth not; and it shall be given him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/24-jeremiah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/24-jeremiah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The words of Jeremiah the son of Hilkiah, of the priests that were in Anathoth in the land of Benjamin:
[1:2] To whom the word of the LORD came in the days of Josiah the son of Amon king of Judah, in the thirteenth year of his reign.
[1:3] It came also in the days of Jehoiakim the son of Josiah king of Judah, unto the end of the eleventh year of Zedekiah the son of Josiah king of Judah, unto the carrying away of Jerusalem captive in the fifth month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/18-job-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/18-job-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] There was a man in the land of Uz, whose name was Job; and that man was perfect and upright, and one that feared God, and eschewed evil.
[1:2] And there were born unto him seven sons and three daughters.
[1:3] His substance also was seven thousand sheep, and three thousand camels, and five hundred yoke of oxen, and five hundred she asses, and a very great household; so that this man was the greatest of all the men of the east.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/29-joel-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/29-joel-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of the LORD that came to Joel the son of Pethuel.
[1:2] Hear this, ye old men, and give ear, all ye inhabitants of the land. Hath this been in your days, or even in the days of your fathers?
[1:3] Tell ye your children of it, and let your children tell their children, and their children another generation.
[1:4] That which the palmerworm hath left hath the locust eaten; and that which the locust hath left hath the cankerworm eaten; and that which the cankerworm hath left hath the caterpiller eaten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/43-john-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/43-john-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the beginning was the Word, and the Word was with God, and the Word was God.
[1:2] The same was in the beginning with God.
[1:3] All things were made by him; and without him was not any thing made that was made.
[1:4] In him was life; and the life was the light of men.
[1:5] And the light shineth in darkness; and the darkness comprehended it not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/32-jonah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/32-jonah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now the word of the LORD came unto Jonah the son of Amittai, saying,
[1:2] Arise, go to Nineveh, that great city, and cry against it; for their wickedness is come up before me.
[1:3] But Jonah rose up to flee unto Tarshish from the presence of the LORD, and went down to Joppa; and he found a ship going to Tarshish: so he paid the fare thereof, and went down into it, to go with them unto Tarshish from the presence of the LORD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joshua - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/6-joshua-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/6-joshua-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now after the death of Moses the servant of the LORD it came to pass, that the LORD spake unto Joshua the son of Nun, Moses&amp;rsquo; minister, saying,
[1:2] Moses my servant is dead; now therefore arise, go over this Jordan, thou, and all this people, unto the land which I do give to them, even to the children of Israel.
[1:3] Every place that the sole of your foot shall tread upon, that have I given unto you, as I said unto Moses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/65-jude-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/65-jude-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Jude, the servant of Jesus Christ, and brother of James, to them that are sanctified by God the Father, and preserved in Jesus Christ, and called:
[1:2] Mercy unto you, and peace, and love, be multiplied.
[1:3] Beloved, when I gave all diligence to write unto you of the common salvation, it was needful for me to write unto you, and exhort you that ye should earnestly contend for the faith which was once delivered unto the saints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judges - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/7-judges-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/7-judges-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now after the death of Joshua it came to pass, that the children of Israel asked the LORD, saying, Who shall go up for us against the Canaanites first, to fight against them?
[1:2] And the LORD said, Judah shall go up: behold, I have delivered the land into his hand.
[1:3] And Judah said unto Simeon his brother, Come up with me into my lot, that we may fight against the Canaanites; and I likewise will go with thee into thy lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamentations - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/25-lamentations-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/25-lamentations-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] How doth the city sit solitary, that was full of people! how is she become as a widow! she that was great among the nations, and princess among the provinces, how is she become tributary!
[1:2] She weepeth sore in the night, and her tears are on her cheeks: among all her lovers she hath none to comfort her: all her friends have dealt treacherously with her, they are become her enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/3-leviticus-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/3-leviticus-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And the LORD called unto Moses, and spake unto him out of the tabernacle of the congregation, saying,
[1:2] Speak unto the children of Israel, and say unto them, If any man of you bring an offering unto the LORD, ye shall bring your offering of the cattle, even of the herd, and of the flock.
[1:3] If his offering be a burnt sacrifice of the herd, let him offer a male without blemish: he shall offer it of his own voluntary will at the door of the tabernacle of the congregation before the LORD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/42-luke-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/42-luke-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Forasmuch as many have taken in hand to set forth in order a declaration of those things which are most surely believed among us,
[1:2] Even as they delivered them unto us, which from the beginning were eyewitnesses, and ministers of the word;
[1:3] It seemed good to me also, having had perfect understanding of all things from the very first, to write unto thee in order, most excellent Theophilus,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malachi - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/39-malachi-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/39-malachi-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden of the word of the LORD to Israel by Malachi.
[1:2] I have loved you, saith the LORD. Yet ye say, Wherein hast thou loved us? Was not Esau Jacob&amp;rsquo;s brother? saith the LORD: yet I loved Jacob,
[1:3] And I hated Esau, and laid his mountains and his heritage waste for the dragons of the wilderness.
[1:4] Whereas Edom saith, We are impoverished, but we will return and build the desolate places; thus saith the LORD of hosts, They shall build, but I will throw down; and they shall call them, The border of wickedness, and, The people against whom the LORD hath indignation for ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/41-mark-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/41-mark-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The beginning of the gospel of Jesus Christ, the Son of God;
[1:2] As it is written in the prophets, Behold, I send my messenger before thy face, which shall prepare thy way before thee.
[1:3] The voice of one crying in the wilderness, Prepare ye the way of the Lord, make his paths straight.
[1:4] John did baptize in the wilderness, and preach the baptism of repentance for the remission of sins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/40-matthew-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/40-matthew-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The book of the generation of Jesus Christ, the son of David, the son of Abraham.
[1:2] Abraham begat Isaac; and Isaac begat Jacob; and Jacob begat Judas and his brethren;
[1:3] And Judas begat Phares and Zara of Thamar; and Phares begat Esrom; and Esrom begat Aram;
[1:4] And Aram begat Aminadab; and Aminadab begat Naasson; and Naasson begat Salmon;
[1:5] And Salmon begat Booz of Rachab; and Booz begat Obed of Ruth; and Obed begat Jesse;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/33-micah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/33-micah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of the LORD that came to Micah the Morasthite in the days of Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, which he saw concerning Samaria and Jerusalem.
[1:2] Hear, all ye people; hearken, O earth, and all that therein is: and let the Lord GOD be witness against you, the LORD from his holy temple.
[1:3] For, behold, the LORD cometh forth out of his place, and will come down, and tread upon the high places of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nahum - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/34-nahum-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/34-nahum-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The burden of Nineveh. The book of the vision of Nahum the Elkoshite.
[1:2] God is jealous, and the LORD revengeth; the LORD revengeth, and is furious; the LORD will take vengeance on his adversaries, and he reserveth wrath for his enemies.
[1:3] The LORD is slow to anger, and great in power, and will not at all acquit the wicked: the LORD hath his way in the whirlwind and in the storm, and the clouds are the dust of his feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nehemiah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/16-nehemiah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/16-nehemiah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The words of Nehemiah the son of Hachaliah. And it came to pass in the month Chisleu, in the twentieth year, as I was in Shushan the palace,
[1:2] That Hanani, one of my brethren, came, he and certain men of Judah; and I asked them concerning the Jews that had escaped, which were left of the captivity, and concerning Jerusalem.
[1:3] And they said unto me, The remnant that are left of the captivity there in the province are in great affliction and reproach: the wall of Jerusalem also is broken down, and the gates thereof are burned with fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numbers - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/4-numbers-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/4-numbers-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] And the LORD spake unto Moses in the wilderness of Sinai, in the tabernacle of the congregation, on the first day of the second month, in the second year after they were come out of the land of Egypt, saying,
[1:2] Take ye the sum of all the congregation of the children of Israel, after their families, by the house of their fathers, with the number of their names, every male by their polls;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obadiah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/31-obadiah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/31-obadiah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The vision of Obadiah. Thus saith the Lord GOD concerning Edom; We have heard a rumour from the LORD, and an ambassador is sent among the heathen, Arise ye, and let us rise up against her in battle.
[1:2] Behold, I have made thee small among the heathen: thou art greatly despised.
[1:3] The pride of thine heart hath deceived thee, thou that dwellest in the clefts of the rock, whose habitation is high; that saith in his heart, Who shall bring me down to the ground?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philemon - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/57-philemon-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/57-philemon-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, a prisoner of Jesus Christ, and Timothy our brother, unto Philemon our dearly beloved, and fellowlabourer,
[1:2] And to our beloved Apphia, and Archippus our fellowsoldier, and to the church in thy house:
[1:3] Grace to you, and peace, from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:4] I thank my God, making mention of thee always in my prayers,
[1:5] Hearing of thy love and faith, which thou hast toward the Lord Jesus, and toward all saints;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippians - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/50-philippians-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/50-philippians-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul and Timotheus, the servants of Jesus Christ, to all the saints in Christ Jesus which are at Philippi, with the bishops and deacons:
[1:2] Grace be unto you, and peace, from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] I thank my God upon every remembrance of you,
[1:4] Always in every prayer of mine for you all making request with joy,
[1:5] For your fellowship in the gospel from the first day until now;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proverbs - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/20-proverbs-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/20-proverbs-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The proverbs of Solomon the son of David, king of Israel;
[1:2] To know wisdom and instruction; to perceive the words of understanding;
[1:3] To receive the instruction of wisdom, justice, and judgment, and equity;
[1:4] To give subtilty to the simple, to the young man knowledge and discretion.
[1:5] A wise man will hear, and will increase learning; and a man of understanding shall attain unto wise counsels:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psalms - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/19-psalms-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/19-psalms-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Blessed is the man that walketh not in the counsel of the ungodly, nor standeth in the way of sinners, nor sitteth in the seat of the scornful.
[1:2] But his delight is in the law of the LORD; and in his law doth he meditate day and night.
[1:3] And he shall be like a tree planted by the rivers of water, that bringeth forth his fruit in his season; his leaf also shall not wither; and whatsoever he doeth shall prosper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelation - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/66-revelation-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/66-revelation-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Revelation of Jesus Christ, which God gave unto him, to shew unto his servants things which must shortly come to pass; and he sent and signified it by his angel unto his servant John:
[1:2] Who bare record of the word of God, and of the testimony of Jesus Christ, and of all things that he saw.
[1:3] Blessed is he that readeth, and they that hear the words of this prophecy, and keep those things which are written therein: for the time is at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romans - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/45-romans-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/45-romans-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, a servant of Jesus Christ, called to be an apostle, separated unto the gospel of God,
[1:2] (Which he had promised afore by his prophets in the holy scriptures,)
[1:3] Concerning his Son Jesus Christ our Lord, which was made of the seed of David according to the flesh;
[1:4] And declared to be the Son of God with power, according to the spirit of holiness, by the resurrection from the dead:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruth - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/8-ruth-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/8-ruth-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Now it came to pass in the days when the judges ruled, that there was a famine in the land. And a certain man of Bethlehemjudah went to sojourn in the country of Moab, he, and his wife, and his two sons.
[1:2] And the name of the man was Elimelech, and the name of his wife Naomi, and the name of his two sons Mahlon and Chilion, Ephrathites of Bethlehemjudah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song of Solomon - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/22-song-of-solomon-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/22-song-of-solomon-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The song of songs, which is Solomon&amp;rsquo;s.
[1:2] Let him kiss me with the kisses of his mouth: for thy love is better than wine.
[1:3] Because of the savour of thy good ointments thy name is as ointment poured forth, therefore do the virgins love thee.
[1:4] Draw me, we will run after thee: the king hath brought me into his chambers: we will be glad and rejoice in thee, we will remember thy love more than wine: the upright love thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Titus - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/56-titus-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/56-titus-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, a servant of God, and an apostle of Jesus Christ, according to the faith of God&amp;rsquo;s elect, and the acknowledging of the truth which is after godliness;
[1:2] In hope of eternal life, which God, that cannot lie, promised before the world began;
[1:3] But hath in due times manifested his word through preaching, which is committed unto me according to the commandment of God our Saviour;
[1:4] To Titus, mine own son after the common faith: Grace, mercy, and peace, from God the Father and the Lord Jesus Christ our Saviour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zechariah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/38-zechariah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/38-zechariah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] In the eighth month, in the second year of Darius, came the word of the LORD unto Zechariah, the son of Berechiah, the son of Iddo the prophet, saying,
[1:2] The LORD hath been sore displeased with your fathers.
[1:3] Therefore say thou unto them, Thus saith the LORD of hosts; Turn ye unto me, saith the LORD of hosts, and I will turn unto you, saith the LORD of hosts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephaniah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/36-zephaniah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/36-zephaniah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of the LORD which came unto Zephaniah the son of Cushi, the son of Gedaliah, the son of Amariah, the son of Hizkiah, in the days of Josiah the son of Amon, king of Judah.
[1:2] I will utterly consume all things from off the land, saith the LORD.
[1:3] I will consume man and beast; I will consume the fowls of the heaven, and the fishes of the sea, and the stumblingblocks with the wicked: and I will cut off man from off the land, saith the LORD.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>