<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joel on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/joel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Joel on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/joel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/29-joel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/29-joel-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of Jehovah that came to Joel the son of Pethuel.
[1:2] Hear this, ye old men, and give ear, all ye inhabitants of the land. Hath this been in your days, or in the days of your fathers?
[1:3] Tell ye your children of it, and let&#39; your children tell&amp;rsquo; their children, and their children another generation.
[1:4] That which the palmer-worm hath left hath the locust eaten; and that which the locust hath left hath the canker-worm eaten; and that which the canker-worm hath left hath the caterpillar eaten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/29-joel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/29-joel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of the Lord which came to Joel, the son of Pethuel.
[1:2] Give ear to this, you old men, and take note, you people of the land. Has this ever been in your days, or in the days of your fathers?
[1:3] Give the story of it to your children, and let them give it to their children, and their children to another generation.
[1:4] What the worm did not make a meal of, has been taken by the locust; and what the locust did not take, has been food for the plant-worm; and what the plant-worm did not take, has been food for the field-fly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/29-joel-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/29-joel-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The word of the LORD that came to Joel the son of Pethuel.
[1:2] Hear this, ye old men, and give ear, all ye inhabitants of the land. Hath this been in your days, or even in the days of your fathers?
[1:3] Tell ye your children of it, and let your children tell their children, and their children another generation.
[1:4] That which the palmerworm hath left hath the locust eaten; and that which the locust hath left hath the cankerworm eaten; and that which the cankerworm hath left hath the caterpiller eaten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/29-joel-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/29-joel-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Word of Yahweh that came to Joel, the son of Pethuel.
[1:2] Hear this, you elders, And listen, all you inhabitants of the land. Has this ever happened in your days, Or in the days of your fathers?
[1:3] Tell your children about it, And have your children tell their children, And their children, another generation.
[1:4] What the swarming locust has left, the great locust has eaten. What the great locust has left, the grasshopper has eaten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/29-joel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/29-joel-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] A word of Jehovah that hath been unto Joel, son of Pethuel:
[1:2] Hear this, ye aged ones, And give ear, all ye inhabitants of the land, Hath this been in your days? Or in the days of your fathers?
[1:3] Concerning it to your sons talk ye, And your sons to their sons, And their sons to another generation.
[1:4] What is left of the palmer-worm, eaten hath the locust, And what is left of the locust, Eaten hath the cankerworm, And what is left of the cankerworm, Eaten hath the caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>