<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leviticus on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/leviticus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Leviticus on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/leviticus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/3-leviticus-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/3-leviticus-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>Leviticus - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV) [1:1] And Jehovah called unto Moses, and spake unto him out of the tent of meeting, saying,
[1:2] Speak unto the children of Israel, and say unto them, When any man of you offereth an oblation unto Jehovah, ye shall offer your oblation of the cattle, `even&amp;rsquo; of the herd and of the flock.
[1:3] If his oblation be a burnt-offering of the herd, he shall offer it a male without blemish: he shall offer it at the door of the tent of meeting, that he may be accepted before Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/3-leviticus-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/3-leviticus-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Leviticus - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] And the voice of the Lord came to Moses out of the Tent of meeting, saying,
[1:2] Give these orders to the children of Israel: When anyone of you makes an offering to the Lord, you are to take it from the cattle, from the herd or from the flock.
[1:3] If the offering is a burned offering of the herd, let him give a male without a mark: he is to give it at the door of the Tent of meeting so that he may be pleasing to the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/3-leviticus-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/3-leviticus-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>Leviticus - King James Version (KJV) [1:1] And the LORD called unto Moses, and spake unto him out of the tabernacle of the congregation, saying,
[1:2] Speak unto the children of Israel, and say unto them, If any man of you bring an offering unto the LORD, ye shall bring your offering of the cattle, even of the herd, and of the flock.
[1:3] If his offering be a burnt sacrifice of the herd, let him offer a male without blemish: he shall offer it of his own voluntary will at the door of the tabernacle of the congregation before the LORD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/3-leviticus-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/3-leviticus-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>Leviticus - World English Bible (WEB) [1:1] Yahweh called to Moses, and spoke to him out of the Tent of Meeting, saying,
[1:2] &amp;ldquo;Speak to the children of Israel, and tell them, &amp;lsquo;When anyone of you offers an offering to Yahweh, you shall offer your offering of the cattle, from the herd and from the flock.
[1:3] &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;If his offering is a burnt offering from the herd, he shall offer a male without blemish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/3-leviticus-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/3-leviticus-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Leviticus - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] And Jehovah calleth unto Moses, and speaketh unto him out of the tent of meeting, saying,
[1:2] `Speak unto the sons of Israel, and thou hast said unto them, Any man of you when he doth bring near an offering to Jehovah, out of the cattle &amp;ndash; out of the herd, or out of the flock &amp;ndash; ye do bring near your offering.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>