<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 Timothy on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/1-timothy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 Timothy on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/1-timothy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Timothy - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/54-1-timothy-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/54-1-timothy-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Christ Jesus according to the commandment of God our Saviour, and Christ Jesus our hope;
[1:2] unto Timothy, my true child in faith: Grace, mercy, peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] As I exhorted thee to tarry at Ephesus, when I was going into Macedonia, that thou mightest charge certain men not to teach a different doctrine,
[1:4] neither to give heed to fables and endless genealogies, which minister questionings, rather than a dispensation of God which is in faith; `so do I now&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Timothy - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/54-1-timothy-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/54-1-timothy-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an Apostle of Jesus Christ, by the order of God our Saviour and Christ Jesus our hope;
[1:2] To Timothy, my true child in the faith: Grace, mercy, peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] It was my desire, when I went on into Macedonia, that you might make a stop at Ephesus, to give orders to certain men not to put forward a different teaching,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Timothy - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/54-1-timothy-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/54-1-timothy-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ by the commandment of God our Saviour, and Lord Jesus Christ, which is our hope;
[1:2] Unto Timothy, my own son in the faith: Grace, mercy, and peace, from God our Father and Jesus Christ our Lord.
[1:3] As I besought thee to abide still at Ephesus, when I went into Macedonia, that thou mightest charge some that they teach no other doctrine,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Timothy - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/54-1-timothy-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/54-1-timothy-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Christ Jesus according to the commandment of God our Savior, and Christ Jesus our hope;
[1:2] to Timothy, my true child in faith: Grace, mercy, and peace, from God our Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] As I exhorted you to stay at Ephesus when I was going into Macedonia, that you might charge certain men not to teach a different doctrine,
[1:4] neither to pay attention to myths and endless genealogies, which cause disputes, rather than God&amp;rsquo;s stewardship, which is in faith&amp;ndash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Timothy - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/54-1-timothy-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/54-1-timothy-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ, according to a command of God our Saviour, and of the Lord Jesus Christ our hope,
[1:2] to Timotheus &amp;ndash; genuine child in faith: Grace, kindness, peace, from God our Father, and Christ Jesus our Lord,
[1:3] according as I did exhort thee to remain in Ephesus &amp;ndash; I going on to Macedonia &amp;ndash; that thou mightest charge certain not to teach any other thing,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>