<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BBE on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/bbe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BBE on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/bbe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Chronicles - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/13-1-chronicles-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/13-1-chronicles-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>1 Chronicles - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Adam, Seth, Enosh;
[1:2] Kenan, Mahalalel, Jared,
[1:3] Enoch, Methuselah, Lamech;
[1:4] Noah, Shem, Ham, and Japheth.
[1:5] The sons of Japheth: Gomer and Magog and Madai and Javan and Tubal and Meshech and Tiras.
[1:6] And the sons of Gomer: Ashkenaz and Diphath and Togarmah.
[1:7] And the sons of Javan: Elishah and Tarshish, Kittim and Rodanim.
[1:8] The sons of Ham: Cush and Egypt, Put and Canaan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/46-1-corinthians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/46-1-corinthians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>1 Corinthians - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul, an Apostle of Jesus Christ by the purpose of God, and Sosthenes the brother,
[1:2] To the church of God which is in Corinth, to those who have been made holy in Christ Jesus, saints by the selection of God, with all those who in every place give honour to the name of our Lord Jesus Christ, their Lord and ours:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 John - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/62-1-john-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/62-1-john-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>1 John - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] That which was from the first, which has come to our ears, and which we have seen with our eyes, looking on it and touching it with our hands, about the Word of life
[1:2] (And the life was made clear to us, and we have seen it and are witnessing to it and giving you word of that eternal life which was with the Father and was seen by us);</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Kings - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/11-1-kings-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/11-1-kings-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>1 Kings - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Now King David was old and far on in years; and though they put covers over him, his body was cold.
[1:2] So his servants said to him, Let search be made for a young virgin for my lord the king, to take care of him and be waiting on him; and you may take her in your arms, and so my lord the king will be warm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Peter - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/60-1-peter-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/60-1-peter-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>1 Peter - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Peter, an Apostle of Jesus Christ, to the saints who are living in Pontus, Galatia, Cappadocia, Asia, and Bithynia,
[1:2] Who, through the purpose of God, have been made holy by the Spirit, disciples of Jesus, made clean by his blood: May you have grace and peace in full measure.
[1:3] Praise be to the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who through his great mercy has given us a new birth and a living hope by the coming again of Jesus Christ from the dead,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Samuel - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/9-1-samuel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/9-1-samuel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>1 Samuel - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Now there was a certain man of Ramathaim, a Zuphite of the hill-country of Ephraim, named Elkanah; he was the son of Jeroham, the son of Elihu, the son of Tohu, the son of Zuph, an Ephraimite:
[1:2] And he had two wives, one named Hannah and the other Peninnah: and Peninnah was the mother of children, but Hannah had no children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Thessalonians - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/52-1-thessalonians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/52-1-thessalonians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>1 Thessalonians - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul and Silvanus and Timothy, to the church of the Thessalonians in God the Father and the Lord Jesus Christ: Grace to you and peace.
[1:2] We give praise to God at all times for you, keeping you in memory in our prayers;
[1:3] Having ever in mind your work of faith and acts of love and the strength of your hope in our Lord Jesus Christ, before our God and Father;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Timothy - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/54-1-timothy-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/54-1-timothy-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>1 Timothy - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul, an Apostle of Jesus Christ, by the order of God our Saviour and Christ Jesus our hope;
[1:2] To Timothy, my true child in the faith: Grace, mercy, peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] It was my desire, when I went on into Macedonia, that you might make a stop at Ephesus, to give orders to certain men not to put forward a different teaching,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Chronicles - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/14-2-chronicles-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/14-2-chronicles-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>2 Chronicles - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] And Solomon, the son of David, made himself strong in his kingdom, and the Lord his God was with him, and made him very great.
[1:2] And Solomon sent word to all Israel, to the captains of thousands and of hundreds and to the judges and to every chief in all Israel, heads of their families.
[1:3] Then Solomon, and all the men of Israel with him, went to the high place at Gibeon, because the Tent of meeting of God, which Moses, the servant of the Lord, had made in the waste land, was there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Corinthians - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/47-2-corinthians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/47-2-corinthians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>2 Corinthians - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul, an Apostle of Jesus Christ by the purpose of God, and Timothy the brother, to the church of God which is in Corinth, with all the saints who are in all Achaia:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] Praise be to the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, the Father of mercies and the God of all comfort;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 John - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/63-2-john-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/63-2-john-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>2 John - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] I, a ruler in the church, send word to the noble sister who is of God&amp;rsquo;s selection, and to her children, for whom I have true love; and not only I, but all who have knowledge of what is true;
[1:2] Because of this true knowledge which is in us, and will be with us for ever:
[1:3] May grace, mercy, and peace be with us from God the Father, and from Jesus Christ, the Son of the Father, in all true love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Kings - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/12-2-kings-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/12-2-kings-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>2 Kings - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] After the death of Ahab, Moab made itself free from the authority of Israel.
[1:2] Now Ahaziah had a fall from the window of his room in Samaria, and was ill. And he sent men, and said to them, Put a question to Baal-zebub, the god of Ekron, about the outcome of my disease, to see if I will get well or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Peter - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/61-2-peter-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/61-2-peter-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>2 Peter - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Simon Peter, a servant and Apostle of Jesus Christ, to those who with us have a part in the same holy faith in the righteousness of our God and Saviour Jesus Christ:
[1:2] May grace and peace ever be increasing in you, in the knowledge of God and of Jesus our Lord;
[1:3] Because by his power he has given us everything necessary for life and righteousness, through the knowledge of him who has been our guide by his glory and virtue;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Samuel - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/10-2-samuel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/10-2-samuel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>2 Samuel - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Now after the death of Saul, when David, having come back from the destruction of the Amalekites, had been in Ziklag for two days;
[1:2] On the third day a man came from Saul&amp;rsquo;s tents, with his clothing out of order and earth on his head: and when he came to David, he went down on the earth and gave him honour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Thessalonians - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/53-2-thessalonians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/53-2-thessalonians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>2 Thessalonians - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul and Silvanus and Timothy, to the church of the Thessalonians in God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God the Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] It is right for us to give praise to God at all times for you, brothers, because of the great increase of your faith, and the wealth of your love for one another;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Timothy - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/55-2-timothy-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/55-2-timothy-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>2 Timothy - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul, an Apostle of Jesus Christ by the purpose of God, in the hope of the life which is in Christ Jesus,
[1:2] To Timothy, my well-loved child: Grace, mercy, peace, from God the Father and Christ Jesus our Lord.
[1:3] I give praise to God, whose servant I have been, with a heart free from sin, from the time of my fathers, because in my prayers at all times the thought of you is with me, night and day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 John - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/64-3-john-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/64-3-john-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>3 John - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] I, a ruler in the church, send word to the well loved Gaius, for whom I have true love.
[1:2] My loved one, it is my prayer that you may do well in all things, and be healthy in body, even as your soul does well.
[1:3] For it gave me great joy when some of the brothers came and gave witness that you had the true faith and were walking in the true way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acts - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/44-acts-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/44-acts-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Acts - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] I have given an earlier account, O Theophilus, of all the things which Jesus did, and of his teaching from the first,
[1:2] Till the day when he was taken up to heaven after he had given his orders, through the Holy Spirit, to the Apostles of whom he had made selection:
[1:3] And to whom he gave clear and certain signs that he was living, after his death; for he was seen by them for forty days, and gave them teaching about the kingdom of God:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amos - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/30-amos-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/30-amos-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Amos - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The words of Amos, who was among the herdsmen of Tekoa; what he saw about Israel in the days of Uzziah, king of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam, the son of Joash, king of Israel, two years before the earth-shock.
[1:2] And he said, The Lord will give a lion&amp;rsquo;s cry from Zion, his voice will be sounding from Jerusalem; and the fields of the keepers of sheep will become dry, and the top of Carmel will be wasted away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colossians - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/51-colossians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/51-colossians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Colossians - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul, an Apostle of Jesus Christ, by the purpose of God, and Timothy our brother,
[1:2] To the saints and true brothers in Christ at Colossae: Grace to you and peace from God our Father.
[1:3] We give praise to God the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, making prayer for you at all times,
[1:4] After hearing of your faith in Christ Jesus, and of the love which you have for all the saints,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/27-daniel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/27-daniel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Daniel - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] In the third year of the rule of Jehoiakim, king of Judah, Nebuchadnezzar, king of Babylon, came to Jerusalem, shutting it in with his forces.
[1:2] And the Lord gave into his hands Jehoiakim, king of Judah, with some of the vessels of the house of God; and he took them away into the land of Shinar to the house of his god; and he put the vessels into the store-house of his god.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deuteronomy - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/5-deuteronomy-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/5-deuteronomy-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Deuteronomy - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] These are the words which Moses said to all Israel on the far side of Jordan, in the waste land in the Arabah opposite Suph, between Paran on the one side, and Tophel, Laban, Hazeroth, and Dizahab on the other.
[1:2] It is eleven days&amp;rsquo; journey from Horeb by the way of Mount Seir to Kadesh-barnea.
[1:3] Now in the fortieth year, on the first day of the eleventh month, Moses gave to the children of Israel all the orders which the Lord had given him for them;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecclesiastes - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/21-ecclesiastes-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/21-ecclesiastes-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Ecclesiastes - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The words of the Preacher, the son of David, king in Jerusalem.
[1:2] All is to no purpose, said the Preacher, all the ways of man are to no purpose.
[1:3] What is a man profited by all his work which he does under the sun?
[1:4] One generation goes and another comes; but the earth is for ever.
[1:5] The sun comes up and the sun goes down, and goes quickly back to the place where he came up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ephesians - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/49-ephesians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/49-ephesians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Ephesians - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul, an Apostle of Christ Jesus by the purpose of God, to the saints who are at Ephesus, and those who have faith in Christ Jesus:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] Praise be to the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who has given us every blessing of the Spirit in the heavens in Christ:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/17-esther-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/17-esther-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Esther - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Now it came about in the days of Ahasuerus, (that Ahasuerus who was ruler of a hundred and twenty-seven divisions of the kingdom, from India as far as Ethiopia:)
[1:2] That in those days, when King Ahasuerus was ruling in Shushan, his strong town,
[1:3] In the third year of his rule he gave a feast to all his captains and his servants; and the captains of the army of Persia and Media, the great men and the rulers of the divisions of his kingdom, were present before him;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exodus - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/2-exodus-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/2-exodus-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Exodus - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Now these are the names of the sons of Israel who came into Egypt; every man and his family came with Jacob.
[1:2] Reuben, Simeon, Levi, and Judah;
[1:3] Issachar, Zebulun, and Benjamin;
[1:4] Dan and Naphtali, Gad and Asher.
[1:5] All the offspring of Jacob were seventy persons: and Joseph had come to Egypt before them.
[1:6] Then Joseph came to his end, and all his brothers, and all that generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/26-ezekiel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/26-ezekiel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Ezekiel - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Now it came about in the thirtieth year, in the fourth month, on the fifth day of the month, while I was by the river Chebar among those who had been made prisoners, that the heavens were made open and I saw visions of God.
[1:2] On the fifth day of the month, in the fifth year after King Jehoiachin had been made a prisoner,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezra - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/15-ezra-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/15-ezra-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Ezra - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Now in the first year of Cyrus, king of Persia, in order that the word of the Lord given by the mouth of Jeremiah might come true, the spirit of Cyrus, king of Persia, was moved by the Lord, so that he made a public statement through all his kingdom, and put it in writing, saying,
[1:2] These are the words of Cyrus, king of Persia: The Lord God of heaven has given me all the kingdoms of the earth; and he has made me responsible for building a house for him in Jerusalem, which is in Judah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galatians - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/48-galatians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/48-galatians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Galatians - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul, an Apostle (not from men, and not through man, but through Jesus Christ, and God the Father, who made him come back from the dead),
[1:2] And all the brothers who are with me, to the churches of Galatia:
[1:3] Grace to you and peace from God the Father and our Lord Jesus Christ,
[1:4] Who gave himself for our sins, so that he might make us free from this present evil world, after the purpose of our God and Father:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/1-genesis-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/1-genesis-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Genesis - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] At the first God made the heaven and the earth.
[1:2] And the earth was waste and without form; and it was dark on the face of the deep: and the Spirit of God was moving on the face of the waters.
[1:3] And God said, Let there be light: and there was light.
[1:4] And God, looking on the light, saw that it was good: and God made a division between the light and the dark,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habakkuk - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/35-habakkuk-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/35-habakkuk-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Habakkuk - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The word which Habakkuk the prophet saw.
[1:2] How long, O Lord, will your ears be shut to my voice? I make an outcry to you about violent behaviour, but you do not send salvation.
[1:3] Why do you make me see evil-doing, and why are my eyes fixed on wrong? for wasting and violent acts are before me: and there is fighting and bitter argument.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haggai - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/37-haggai-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/37-haggai-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Haggai - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] In the second year of Darius the king, in the sixth month, on the first day of the month, came the word of the Lord by Haggai the prophet to Zerubbabel, the son of Shealtiel, ruler of Judah, and to Joshua, the son of Jehozadak, the high priest, saying,
[1:2] These are the words of the Lord of armies: These people say, The time has not come for building the Lord&amp;rsquo;s house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hebrews - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/58-hebrews-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/58-hebrews-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Hebrews - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] In times past the word of God came to our fathers through the prophets, in different parts and in different ways;
[1:2] But now, at the end of these days, it has come to us through his Son, to whom he has given all things for a heritage, and through whom he made the order of the generations;
[1:3] Who, being the outshining of his glory, the true image of his substance, supporting all things by the word of his power, having given himself as an offering making clean from sins, took his seat at the right hand of God in heaven;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/28-hosea-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/28-hosea-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Hosea - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The word of the Lord which came to Hosea, the son of Beeri, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam, the son of Joash, king of Israel.
[1:2] The start of the word of the Lord by Hosea: And the Lord said to Hosea, Go, take for yourself a wife of loose ways, and children of the same, for the land has been untrue to the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/23-isaiah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/23-isaiah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Isaiah - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The vision of Isaiah, the son of Amoz, which he saw about Judah and Jerusalem, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah.
[1:2] Give ear, O heavens, and you, O earth, to the word which the Lord has said: I have taken care of my children till they became men, but their hearts have been turned away from me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/59-james-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/59-james-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>James - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] James, a servant of God and of the Lord Jesus Christ, sends words of love to the twelve tribes of the Jews living in all parts of the earth.
[1:2] Let it be all joy to you, my brothers, when you undergo tests of every sort;
[1:3] Because you have the knowledge that the testing of your faith gives you the power of going on in hope;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeremiah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/24-jeremiah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/24-jeremiah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Jeremiah - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The words of Jeremiah, the son of Hilkiah, of the priests who were in Anathoth in the land of Benjamin:
[1:2] To whom the word of the Lord came in the days of Josiah, the son of Amon, king of Judah, in the thirteenth year of his rule.
[1:3] And it came again in the days of Jehoiakim, the son of Josiah, king of Judah, up to the eleventh year of Zedekiah, the son of Josiah, king of Judah; till Jerusalem was taken away in the fifth month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/18-job-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/18-job-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Job - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] There was a man in the land of Uz whose name was Job. He was without sin and upright, fearing God and keeping himself far from evil.
[1:2] And he had seven sons and three daughters.
[1:3] And of cattle he had seven thousand sheep and goats, and three thousand camels, and a thousand oxen, and five hundred she-asses, and a very great number of servants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/29-joel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/29-joel-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Joel - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The word of the Lord which came to Joel, the son of Pethuel.
[1:2] Give ear to this, you old men, and take note, you people of the land. Has this ever been in your days, or in the days of your fathers?
[1:3] Give the story of it to your children, and let them give it to their children, and their children to another generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/43-john-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/43-john-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>John - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] From the first he was the Word, and the Word was in relation with God and was God.
[1:2] This Word was from the first in relation with God.
[1:3] All things came into existence through him, and without him nothing was.
[1:4] What came into existence in him was life, and the life was the light of men.
[1:5] And the light goes on shining in the dark; it is not overcome by the dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/32-jonah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/32-jonah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Jonah - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] And the word of the Lord came to Jonah, the son of Amittai, saying,
[1:2] Up! go to Nineveh, that great town, and let your voice come to it; for their evil-doing has come up before me.
[1:3] And Jonah got up to go in flight to Tarshish, away from the Lord; and he went down to Joppa, and saw there a ship going to Tarshish: so he gave them the price of the journey and went down into it to go with them to Tarshish, away from the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joshua - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/6-joshua-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/6-joshua-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Joshua - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Now after the death of Moses, the servant of the Lord, the word of the Lord came to Joshua, the son of Nun, Moses&amp;rsquo; helper, saying,
[1:2] Moses my servant is dead; so now get up! Go over Jordan, you and all this people, into the land which I am giving to them, to the children of Israel.
[1:3] Every place on which you put your foot I have given to you, as I said to Moses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/65-jude-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/65-jude-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Jude - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Jude, a servant of Jesus Christ and the brother of James, to those of God&amp;rsquo;s selection who have been made holy by God the Father and are kept safe for Jesus Christ:
[1:2] May mercy and peace and love be increased in you.
[1:3] My loved ones, while my thoughts were full of a letter which I was going to send you about our common salvation, it was necessary for me to send you one requesting you with all my heart to go on fighting strongly for the faith which has been given to the saints once and for ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judges - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/7-judges-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/7-judges-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Judges - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Now after the death of Joshua, the children of Israel made request to the Lord, saying, Who is to go up first to make war for us against the Canaanites?
[1:2] And the Lord said, Judah is to go up: see, I have given the land into his hands.
[1:3] Then Judah said to Simeon his brother, Come up with me into my heritage, so that we may make war against the Canaanites; and I will then go with you into your heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamentations - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/25-lamentations-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/25-lamentations-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Lamentations - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] See her seated by herself, the town which was full of people! She who was great among the nations has become like a widow! She who was a princess among the countries has come under the yoke of forced work!
[1:2] She is sorrowing bitterly in the night, and her face is wet with weeping; among all her lovers she has no comforter: all her friends have been false to her, they have become her haters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leviticus - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/3-leviticus-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/3-leviticus-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Leviticus - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] And the voice of the Lord came to Moses out of the Tent of meeting, saying,
[1:2] Give these orders to the children of Israel: When anyone of you makes an offering to the Lord, you are to take it from the cattle, from the herd or from the flock.
[1:3] If the offering is a burned offering of the herd, let him give a male without a mark: he is to give it at the door of the Tent of meeting so that he may be pleasing to the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/42-luke-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/42-luke-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Luke - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] As a number of attempts have been made to put together in order an account of those events which took place among us,
[1:2] As they were handed down to us by those who saw them from the first and were preachers of the word,
[1:3] It seemed good to me, having made observation, with great care, of the direction of events in their order, to put the facts in writing for you, most noble Theophilus;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malachi - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/39-malachi-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/39-malachi-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Malachi - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The word of the Lord to Israel by Malachi.
[1:2] You have been loved by me, says the Lord. But you say, Where was your love for us? Was not Esau Jacob&amp;rsquo;s brother? says the Lord: but Jacob was loved by me,
[1:3] And Esau was hated, and I sent destruction on his mountains, and gave his heritage to the beasts of the waste land.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/41-mark-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/41-mark-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Mark - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The first words of the good news of Jesus Christ, the Son of God.
[1:2] Even as it is said in the book of Isaiah the prophet, See, I send my servant before your face, who will make ready your way;
[1:3] The voice of one crying in the waste land, Make ready the way of the Lord, make his roads straight;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/40-matthew-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/40-matthew-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Matthew - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The book of the generations of Jesus Christ, the son of David, the son of Abraham.
[1:2] The son of Abraham was Isaac; and the son of Isaac was Jacob; and the sons of Jacob were Judah and his brothers;
[1:3] And the sons of Judah were Perez and Zerah by Tamar; and the son of Perez was Hezron; and the son of Hezron was Ram;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/33-micah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/33-micah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Micah - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The word of the Lord which came to Micah the Morashtite, in the days of Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah: his vision about Samaria and Jerusalem.
[1:2] Give ear, you peoples, all of you; give attention, O earth and everything in it: let the Lord God be witness against you, the Lord from his holy Temple.
[1:3] For see, the Lord is coming out from his place, and will come down, stepping on the high places of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nahum - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/34-nahum-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/34-nahum-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Nahum - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The word about Nineveh. The book of the vision of Nahum the Elkoshite.
[1:2] The Lord is a God who takes care of his honour and gives punishment for wrong; the Lord gives punishment and is angry; the Lord sends punishment on those who are against him, being angry with his haters.
[1:3] The Lord is slow to get angry and great in power, and will not let the sinner go without punishment: the way of the Lord is in the wind and the storm, and the clouds are the dust of his feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nehemiah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/16-nehemiah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/16-nehemiah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Nehemiah - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The history of Nehemiah, the son of Hacaliah. Now it came about, in the month Chislev, in the twentieth year, when I was in Shushan, the king&amp;rsquo;s town,
[1:2] That Hanani, one of my brothers, came with certain men from Judah; and in answer to my request for news of the Jews who had been prisoners and had got away, and of Jerusalem,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numbers - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/4-numbers-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/4-numbers-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Numbers - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] And the Lord said to Moses in the waste land of Sinai, in the Tent of meeting, on the first day of the second month, in the second year after they came out of the land of Egypt,
[1:2] Take the full number of the children of Israel, by their families, and by their fathers&amp;rsquo; houses, every male by name;
[1:3] All those of twenty years old and over, who are able to go to war in Israel, are to be numbered by you and Aaron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obadiah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/31-obadiah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/31-obadiah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Obadiah - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The vision of Obadiah. This is what the Lord has said about Edom: We have had word from the Lord, and a representative has been sent among the nations, saying, Up! and let us make war against her.
[1:2] See, I have made you small among the nations: you are much looked down on.
[1:3] You have been tricked by the pride of your heart, O you whose living-place is in the cracks of the rock, whose house is high up; who has said in his heart, Who will make me come down to earth?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philemon - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/57-philemon-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/57-philemon-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Philemon - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul, a prisoner of Jesus Christ, and Timothy our brother, to Philemon, our dear helper in the faith,
[1:2] And to Apphia, our sister, and to Archippus, our brother in God&amp;rsquo;s army, and to the church in your house:
[1:3] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:4] I give praise to God at all times and make prayer for you,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippians - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/50-philippians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/50-philippians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Philippians - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul and Timothy, servants of Jesus Christ, to all the saints in Christ Jesus at Philippi, with the Bishops and Deacons of the church:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] I give praise to my God at every memory of you,
[1:4] And in all my prayers for you all, making my request with joy,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proverbs - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/20-proverbs-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/20-proverbs-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Proverbs - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The wise sayings of Solomon, the son of David, king of Israel.
[1:2] To have knowledge of wise teaching; to be clear about the words of reason:
[1:3] To be trained in the ways of wisdom, in righteousness and judging truly and straight behaviour:
[1:4] To make the simple-minded sharp, and to give the young man knowledge, and serious purpose:
[1:5] (The wise man, hearing, will get greater learning, and the acts of the man of good sense will be wisely guided:)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psalms - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/19-psalms-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/19-psalms-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Psalms - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Happy is the man who does not go in the company of sinners, or take his place in the way of evil-doers, or in the seat of those who do not give honour to the Lord.
[1:2] But whose delight is in the law of the Lord, and whose mind is on his law day and night.
[1:3] He will be like a tree planted by the rivers of water, which gives its fruit at the right time, whose leaves will ever be green; and he will do well in all his undertakings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelation - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/66-revelation-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/66-revelation-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Revelation - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The Revelation of Jesus Christ which God gave him so that his servants might have knowledge of the things which will quickly take place: and he sent and made it clear by his angel to his servant John;
[1:2] Who gave witness of the word of God, and of the witness of Jesus Christ, even of all the things which he saw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romans - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/45-romans-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/45-romans-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Romans - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul, a servant of Jesus Christ, an Apostle by the selection of God, given authority as a preacher of the good news,
[1:2] Of which God had given word before by his prophets in the holy Writings,
[1:3] About his Son who, in the flesh, came from the family of David,
[1:4] But was marked out as Son of God in power by the Holy Spirit through the coming to life again of the dead; Jesus Christ our Lord,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruth - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/8-ruth-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/8-ruth-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Ruth - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Now there came a time, in the days of the judges, when there was no food in the land. And a certain man went from Beth-lehem-judah, he and his wife and his two sons, to make a living-place in the country of Moab.
[1:2] And the name of the man was Elimelech, and the name of his wife Naomi, and the name of his two sons Mahlon and Chilion, Ephrathites of Beth-lehem-judah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song of Solomon - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/22-song-of-solomon-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/22-song-of-solomon-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Song of Solomon - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The song of Songs, which is Solomon&amp;rsquo;s.
[1:2] Let him give me the kisses of his mouth: for his love is better than wine.
[1:3] Sweet is the smell of your perfumes; your name is as perfume running out; so the young girls give you their love.
[1:4] Take me to you, and we will go after you: the king has taken me into his house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Titus - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/56-titus-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/56-titus-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Titus - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] Paul, a servant of God, and an Apostle of Jesus Christ, in agreement with the faith of the saints of God and the full knowledge of what is true in harmony with religion,
[1:2] In the hope of eternal life, which was made certain before eternal time, by the word of God who is ever true;
[1:3] Who, in his time, made clear his word in the good news, of which, by the order of God our Saviour, I became a preacher;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zechariah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/38-zechariah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/38-zechariah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Zechariah - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] In the eighth month, in the second year of Darius, the word of the Lord came to Zechariah, the son of Berechiah, the son of Iddo the prophet, saying,
[1:2] The Lord has been very angry with your fathers:
[1:3] And you are to say to them, These are the words of the Lord of armies: Come back to me, says the Lord of armies, and I will come back to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephaniah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/36-zephaniah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/36-zephaniah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Zephaniah - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The word of the Lord which came to Zephaniah, the son of Cushi, the son of Gedaliah, the son of Amariah, the son of Hezekiah, in the days of Josiah, the son of Amon, king of Judah.
[1:2] I will take away everything from the face of the earth, says the Lord.
[1:3] I will take away man and beast; I will take away the birds of the heaven and the fishes of the sea; causing the downfall of the evil-doers, and cutting man off from the face of the earth, says the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>