<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Job on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/job/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Job on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Job - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/18-job-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/18-job-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>Job - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV) [1:1] There was a man in the land of Uz, whose name was Job; and that man was perfect and upright, and one that feared God, and turned away from evil.
[1:2] And there were born unto him seven sons and three daughters.
[1:3] His substance also was seven thousand sheep, and three thousand camels, and five hundred yoke of oxen, and five hundred she-asses, and a very great household; so that this man was the greatest of all the children of the east.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/18-job-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/18-job-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Job - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] There was a man in the land of Uz whose name was Job. He was without sin and upright, fearing God and keeping himself far from evil.
[1:2] And he had seven sons and three daughters.
[1:3] And of cattle he had seven thousand sheep and goats, and three thousand camels, and a thousand oxen, and five hundred she-asses, and a very great number of servants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/18-job-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/18-job-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>Job - King James Version (KJV) [1:1] There was a man in the land of Uz, whose name was Job; and that man was perfect and upright, and one that feared God, and eschewed evil.
[1:2] And there were born unto him seven sons and three daughters.
[1:3] His substance also was seven thousand sheep, and three thousand camels, and five hundred yoke of oxen, and five hundred she asses, and a very great household; so that this man was the greatest of all the men of the east.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/18-job-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/18-job-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>Job - World English Bible (WEB) [1:1] There was a man in the land of Uz, whose name was Job. That man was blameless and upright, and one who feared God, and turned away from evil.
[1:2] There were born to him seven sons and three daughters.
[1:3] His possessions also were seven thousand sheep, three thousand camels, five hundred yoke of oxen, five hundred she-donkeys, and a very great household; so that this man was the greatest of all the children of the east.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/18-job-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/18-job-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Job - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A man there hath been in the land of Uz &amp;ndash; Job his name &amp;ndash; and that man hath been perfect and upright &amp;ndash; both fearing God, and turning aside from evil.
[1:2] And there are borne to him seven sons and three daughters,
[1:3] and his substance is seven thousand sheep, and three thousand camels, and five hundred pairs of oxen, and five hundred she-asses, and a service very abundant; and that man is greater than any of the sons of the east.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>