<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ephesians on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/ephesians/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ephesians on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/ephesians/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ephesians - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/49-ephesians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/49-ephesians-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Christ Jesus through the will of God, to the saints that are at Ephesus, and the faithful in Christ Jesus:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] Blessed be&#39; the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who hath blessed us with every spiritual blessing in the heavenly places&amp;rsquo; in Christ:
[1:4] even as he chose us in him before the foundation of the world, that we should be holy and without blemish before him in love:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ephesians - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/49-ephesians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/49-ephesians-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an Apostle of Christ Jesus by the purpose of God, to the saints who are at Ephesus, and those who have faith in Christ Jesus:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] Praise be to the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who has given us every blessing of the Spirit in the heavens in Christ:
[1:4] Even as he made selection of us in him from the first, so that we might be holy and free from all evil before him in love:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ephesians - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/49-ephesians-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/49-ephesians-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ by the will of God, to the saints which are at Ephesus, and to the faithful in Christ Jesus:
[1:2] Grace be to you, and peace, from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] Blessed be the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who hath blessed us with all spiritual blessings in heavenly places in Christ:
[1:4] According as he hath chosen us in him before the foundation of the world, that we should be holy and without blame before him in love:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ephesians - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/49-ephesians-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/49-ephesians-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Christ Jesus through the will of God, to the saints who are at Ephesus, and the faithful in Christ Jesus:
[1:2] Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.
[1:3] Blessed be the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who has blessed us with every spiritual blessing in the heavenly places in Christ;
[1:4] even as he chose us in him before the foundation of the world, that we would be holy and without blemish before him in love;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ephesians - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/49-ephesians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/49-ephesians-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ through the will of God, to the saints who are in Ephesus, and to the faithful in Christ Jesus:
[1:2] Grace to you, and peace from God our Father, and the Lord Jesus Christ!
[1:3] Blessed `is&amp;rsquo; the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who did bless us in every spiritual blessing in the heavenly places in Christ,
[1:4] according as He did choose us in him before the foundation of the world, for our being holy and unblemished before Him, in love,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>