<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lamentations on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/lamentations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lamentations on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/lamentations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamentations - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/25-lamentations-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/25-lamentations-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>Lamentations - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV) [1:1] How doth the city sit solitary, that was full of people! She is become as a widow, that was great among the nations! She that was a princess among the provinces is become tributary!
[1:2] She weepeth sore in the night, and her tears are on her cheeks; Among all her lovers she hath none to comfort her: All her friends have dealt treacherously with her; they are become her enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamentations - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/25-lamentations-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/25-lamentations-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Lamentations - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] See her seated by herself, the town which was full of people! She who was great among the nations has become like a widow! She who was a princess among the countries has come under the yoke of forced work!
[1:2] She is sorrowing bitterly in the night, and her face is wet with weeping; among all her lovers she has no comforter: all her friends have been false to her, they have become her haters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamentations - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/25-lamentations-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/25-lamentations-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>Lamentations - King James Version (KJV) [1:1] How doth the city sit solitary, that was full of people! how is she become as a widow! she that was great among the nations, and princess among the provinces, how is she become tributary!
[1:2] She weepeth sore in the night, and her tears are on her cheeks: among all her lovers she hath none to comfort her: all her friends have dealt treacherously with her, they are become her enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamentations - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/25-lamentations-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/25-lamentations-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>Lamentations - World English Bible (WEB) [1:1] How does the city sit solitary, that was full of people! She has become as a widow, who was great among the nations! She who was a princess among the provinces is become tributary!
[1:2] She weeps sore in the night, and her tears are on her cheeks; Among all her lovers she has none to comfort her: All her friends have dealt treacherously with her; they are become her enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamentations - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/25-lamentations-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/25-lamentations-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Lamentations - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] How hath she sat alone, The city abounding with people! She hath been as a widow, The mighty among nations! Princes among provinces, She hath become tributary!
[1:2] She weepeth sore in the night, And her tear `is&amp;rsquo; on her cheeks, There is no comforter for her out of all her lovers, All her friends dealt treacherously by her, They have been to her for enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>