<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Obadiah on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/obadiah/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Obadiah on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/obadiah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Obadiah - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/31-obadiah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/31-obadiah-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The vision of Obadiah. Thus saith the Lord Jehovah concerning Edom: We have heard tidings from Jehovah, and an ambassador is sent among the nations, `saying&amp;rsquo;, Arise ye, and let us rise up against her in battle.
[1:2] Behold, I have made thee small among the nations: thou art greatly despised.
[1:3] The pride of thy heart hath deceived thee, O thou that dwellest in the clefts of the rock, whose habitation is high; that saith in his heart, Who shall bring me down to the ground?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obadiah - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/31-obadiah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/31-obadiah-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The vision of Obadiah. This is what the Lord has said about Edom: We have had word from the Lord, and a representative has been sent among the nations, saying, Up! and let us make war against her.
[1:2] See, I have made you small among the nations: you are much looked down on.
[1:3] You have been tricked by the pride of your heart, O you whose living-place is in the cracks of the rock, whose house is high up; who has said in his heart, Who will make me come down to earth?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obadiah - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/31-obadiah-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/31-obadiah-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The vision of Obadiah. Thus saith the Lord GOD concerning Edom; We have heard a rumour from the LORD, and an ambassador is sent among the heathen, Arise ye, and let us rise up against her in battle.
[1:2] Behold, I have made thee small among the heathen: thou art greatly despised.
[1:3] The pride of thine heart hath deceived thee, thou that dwellest in the clefts of the rock, whose habitation is high; that saith in his heart, Who shall bring me down to the ground?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obadiah - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/31-obadiah-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/31-obadiah-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The vision of Obadiah. This is what the Lord Yahweh says about Edom. We have heard news from Yahweh, and an ambassador is sent among the nations, saying, &amp;ldquo;Arise, and let&amp;rsquo;s rise up against her in battle.
[1:2] Behold, I have made you small among the nations. You are greatly despised.
[1:3] The pride of your heart has deceived you, you who dwell in the clefts of the rock, whose habitation is high, who says in his heart, &amp;lsquo;Who will bring me down to the ground?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obadiah - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/31-obadiah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/31-obadiah-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] Thus said the Lord Jehovah to Edom, A report we have heard from Jehovah, And an ambassador among nations was sent, `Rise, yea, let us rise against her for battle.&amp;rsquo;
[1:2] Lo, little I have made thee among nations, Despised `art&amp;rsquo; thou exceedingly.
[1:3] The pride of thy heart hath lifted thee up, O dweller in clifts of a rock, (A high place is&#39; his habitation, He is saying in his heart, Who doth bring me down `to&amp;rsquo; earth?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>