<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hosea on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/hosea/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hosea on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/hosea/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/28-hosea-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/28-hosea-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>Hosea - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV) [1:1] The word of Jehovah that came unto Hosea the son of Beeri, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam the son of Joash, king of Israel.
[1:2] When Jehovah spake at the first by Hosea, Jehovah said unto Hosea, Go, take unto thee a wife of whoredom and children of whoredom; for the land doth commit great whoredom, `departing&amp;rsquo; from Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/28-hosea-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/28-hosea-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>Hosea - Bible in Basic English (BBE) [1:1] The word of the Lord which came to Hosea, the son of Beeri, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam, the son of Joash, king of Israel.
[1:2] The start of the word of the Lord by Hosea: And the Lord said to Hosea, Go, take for yourself a wife of loose ways, and children of the same, for the land has been untrue to the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/28-hosea-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/28-hosea-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>Hosea - King James Version (KJV) [1:1] The word of the LORD that came unto Hosea, the son of Beeri, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam the son of Joash, king of Israel.
[1:2] The beginning of the word of the LORD by Hosea. And the LORD said to Hosea, Go, take unto thee a wife of whoredoms and children of whoredoms: for the land hath committed great whoredom, departing from the LORD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/28-hosea-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/28-hosea-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>Hosea - World English Bible (WEB) [1:1] The word of Yahweh that came to Hosea the son of Beeri, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam the son of Joash, king of Israel.
[1:2] When Yahweh spoke at the first by Hosea, Yahweh said to Hosea, &amp;ldquo;Go, take for yourself a wife of prostitution and children of unfaithfulness; for the land commits great adultery against from Yahweh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosea - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/28-hosea-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/28-hosea-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>Hosea - Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation (YLT) [1:1] A word of Jehovah that hath been unto Hosea, son of Beeri, in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, Hezekiah, kings of Judah, and in the days of Jeroboam son of Joash, king of Israel:
[1:2] The commencement of Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s speaking by Hosea. And Jehovah saith unto Hosea, `Go, take to thee a woman of whoredoms, and children of whoredoms, for utterly go a-whoring doth the land from after Jehovah.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>