<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Song of Solomon on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</title>
    <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/song-of-solomon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Song of Solomon on Scrollmapper Biblical Text Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scrollmapper.github.io/categories/song-of-solomon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Song of Solomon - American Standard-ASV1901 (ASV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/22-song-of-solomon-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/asv/22-song-of-solomon-american-standard-asv1901-asv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Song of songs, which is Solomon&amp;rsquo;s.
[1:2] Let him kiss me with the kisses of his mouth; For thy love is better than wine.
[1:3] Thine oils have a goodly fragrance; Thy name is `as&amp;rsquo; oil poured forth; Therefore do the virgins love thee.
[1:4] Draw me; we will run after thee: The king hath brought me into his chambers; We will be glad and rejoice in thee; We will make mention of thy love more than of wine: Rightly do they love thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song of Solomon - Bible in Basic English (BBE)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/22-song-of-solomon-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/bbe/22-song-of-solomon-bible-in-basic-english-bbe/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The song of Songs, which is Solomon&amp;rsquo;s.
[1:2] Let him give me the kisses of his mouth: for his love is better than wine.
[1:3] Sweet is the smell of your perfumes; your name is as perfume running out; so the young girls give you their love.
[1:4] Take me to you, and we will go after you: the king has taken me into his house. We will be glad and full of joy in you, we will give more thought to your love than to wine: rightly are they your lovers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song of Solomon - King James Version (KJV)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/22-song-of-solomon-king-james-version-kjv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/kjv/22-song-of-solomon-king-james-version-kjv/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The song of songs, which is Solomon&amp;rsquo;s.
[1:2] Let him kiss me with the kisses of his mouth: for thy love is better than wine.
[1:3] Because of the savour of thy good ointments thy name is as ointment poured forth, therefore do the virgins love thee.
[1:4] Draw me, we will run after thee: the king hath brought me into his chambers: we will be glad and rejoice in thee, we will remember thy love more than wine: the upright love thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song of Solomon - World English Bible (WEB)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/22-song-of-solomon-world-english-bible-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/web/22-song-of-solomon-world-english-bible-web/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Song of songs, which is Solomon&amp;rsquo;s. Beloved
[1:2] Let him kiss me with the kisses of his mouth; For your love is better than wine.
[1:3] Your oils have a pleasing fragrance. Your name is oil poured forth, Therefore the virgins love you.
[1:4] Take me away with you. Let us hurry. The king has brought me into his chambers. Friends We will be glad and rejoice in you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song of Solomon - Young&#39;s Literal Translation (YLT)</title>
      <link>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/22-song-of-solomon-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:23:55 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scrollmapper.github.io/scrolls/biblical/ylt/22-song-of-solomon-young-s-literal-translation-ylt/</guid>
      <description>[1:1] The Song of Songs, that `is&amp;rsquo; Solomon&amp;rsquo;s.
[1:2] Let him kiss me with kisses of his mouth, For better `are&amp;rsquo; thy loves than wine.
[1:3] For fragrance `are&amp;rsquo; thy perfumes good. Perfume emptied out &amp;ndash; thy name, Therefore have virgins loved thee!
[1:4] Draw me: after thee we run, The king hath brought me into his inner chambers, We do joy and rejoice in thee, We mention thy loves more than wine, Uprightly they have loved thee!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>